有人说 '本事好不如运气好'
the man who said, 'l'd rather be lucky than good,'
说的一点也不错
saw deeply into life.
人们害怕生活中什么都要依赖运气
People are afraid to face how great a part of life is dependent on luck.
他们害怕事情超出自己的控制
lt's scary to think so much is out of one's control.
在网球比赛中 球经常会击中网的上沿
there are moments in a match when the ball hits the top of the net,
在那瞬间 球有可能越过球网或者弹回来
and for a split second it can either go forward or fall back.
如果运气好，它就会越过球网 而你赢得比赛
With a little luck, it goes forward and you win.
又或者它弹回来 你输掉比赛
Or maybe it doesn't, and you lose.
对不起
Sorry.
唐冼德先生
Mr. townsend.
这边请
Just this way.
在马尔贝拉海滩俱乐部 做过网球教练
So the Beach Olub Marbella, tennis instructor.
还在斯坦福楼，撒丁岛，尼斯工作过
Stanford House. Forte village, Sardinia. Nice.
是的 我经验丰富
Yes. l've had a good deal of experience.
嗯，看得出来
Yeah, so l see.
我听说 你不想参加职业比赛
Now, l've heard very good things. You don't miss playing professionally?
我很高兴没有参加
l thank God every day l don't have to do it.
我讨厌网球巡回赛
l hate the whole tennis tour thing.
没完没了的训练 而且我不可能成为卢斯基或者阿加西那样的好手
Oonstant traveling, and l was never going to be Rusedski or Agassi.
没必要非往那方面发展
You have to really want it.
虽然我有他们的天赋
Not that l have their talent.
你的证书和推荐信都非常不错
Well, your credentials and references are excellent.
你想在伦敦生活?
And you want to live in London?
非常想 非常想
very much. very much.
这里的会员非尊则贵
We have a very exclusive membership here.
周末就上班可以吗
You can begin this weekend?
没问题 非常感谢
thank you. thank you very much.
那是沙发 展开可以做床
that's your sofa, which also doubles up as a bed.
非常不错 你可以坐在那看电视
Which is great, you know, 'cause you can be watching some telly,
看累了也不用走去卧室
ain't got the hassle of having to go to a bedroom.
展开就可以睡了
You can just open it up, get your kip.
厨房在那边
kitchen just through there.
设备齐全，干衣机等等
All your amenities, fixtures, fittings, washer dryer...
该有的都有了
All that stuff.
风景也不错，可以远眺
Lovely view, not overlooked.
所有的东西都不错
So it's all good.
一周要225英镑?
this is 225 a week?
这可是伦敦耶，如果你想便宜点的 可以到利兹找找看
Well, it's London, mate. Bang, mate. lf you don't like it, move to Leeds.
了解我的意思吗 你有锅吗
D'you know what l mean? You got a wok?
你有锅吗 就是东方人用的那种圆底锅
You got a wok? lt's one of those Oriental, sort of conical pans.
没有 以前住这的老头
No, no, no. the geezer who was in here before,
留下了一个，如果你想要 我可以留给你
he left one in there. You're welcome to it. l'll throw that in.
我租了 明智的选择
l'll take it. that's a good choice.
很好
very good.
克里斯·维尔顿
Ohris Wilton.
这位是汤姆·休伊特
this is tom Hewett.
你好，很高兴认识你 早上好，我的荣幸
very nice to meet you. How do you do? Morning. Pleasure.
我想克里斯会是你的好教练
l think Ohris would be the perfect instructor for you,
他很有耐心 善于纠正球员的错误
and he's very patient. Great at analyzing a player's faults.
我很久没打了 大学毕业后就没有打过
l'm so out of practice. l mean, l haven't played since university,
我以前很喜欢打 不过好多年没打了
and l loved it, but l haven't picked up a racket in bloody ages, so...
没关系 状态会回来的
Don't worry, it comes back.
只要别急于求成 别气馁就行了
What you can't do is rush in, be discouraged.
没问题
Ok.
祝你好运 非常感谢
Well, good luck. thank you very much.
就在这练吧 好
Over here. Brilliant.
你觉得谁厉害一点 哈曼还是阿加西
Ok, so who was better, or tougher? Henman or Agassi?
他们都很厉害 我知道，我的意思是
they were both great. Yeah, l know, but l mean,
你心里面更倾向谁
you held your own more than admirably.
很难说
For a while.
比赛的时候 你会发现他们真的很棒
But as the game goes on, you see how really good they are.
我来买单 不
Actually, l'll get this. No, no, no, no.
不, 汤姆，让我来吧 不
No, please, tom, l insist. l insist. No, no, no, no, no.
把你慷慨的手挪开吧
Get your dirty great forehand off.
谢谢 下次我买单
thank you. l'll get the next one.
待会你要去举重吗
So, do you need a lift after this?
事实上，我想去找家音像店 我想买些唱片
Actually, l'm looking for a music store. l want to buy some ODs.
这附近吗 我想富汉路上有一家
Music around here? l think there's one on the Fulham Road.
那里有没有歌剧买
And they'll have a decent opera section?
歌剧 你喜欢歌剧, 真的吗
Opera? You like opera, really?
我热爱歌剧
l love opera.
我爸要我们陪他去 皇家加文花园看歌剧
Papa gives loads to the Royal in Oovent Garden.
我知道这有点唐突
l know this is gonna sound a bit weird,
但你有兴趣明晚一起去吗
but would you like to go to the opera tomorrow night?
到歌剧院去?
to the opera?
是的，我们订了包厢 有空出来的票
Yeah. We've got a box and someone's not coming.
上演《La bloody traviata》
lt's La bloody traviata.
天啊，我非常愿意
My God. l'd love to.
你不是听我说喜欢就这样说的吧? 至少能让我付自己的门票吧?
Are you sure it's not an imposition? Oan l at least pay for my seat?
当然不是 你能来是我们的荣幸
lt's not an imposition, it'd be an absolute pleasure.
我非常高兴你我都喜欢歌剧
l just like the fact that we both share a love for opera. Brilliant.
So?
我跟大卫和玛丽纱说... 大家晚上好，妈妈，你好
l said to David and Melissa... Evening all. Hello, Mum.
甜心，见到你真高兴
Hello, sweetie. very nice to see you.
这位是克里斯，这是我爸爸阿莱克 你好，很高兴认识你
this is Ohris. this is my father Alec. Hello. Good to meet you.
我听说你的网球很厉害
l hear you're an incredible tennis player.
我以前也玩过网球，后来放弃了 再后来重新打，没多久又放弃了
l played once, and then l gave up, then l went back, then l gave up,
然后我又开始打 废话
then l went back Rubbish.
一定是汤姆把我夸大其辞了 现在我又不想打了
l'm sure tom exaggerated my game. l just got bored.
晚上好，很荣幸认识你 你好
Good evening. My pleasure. Nice to meet you.
这是我的妹妹克洛伊 那里有椅子
this is my sister... Ohloe. there's a chair somewhere.
我叫克洛伊，很高兴认识你 那边还有两张椅子
l'm Ohloe. Nice to meet you. there's two more.
老家伙很感谢你送他们漂亮的花
Yeah, well, the olds say thank you very much for the lovely flowers.
他们说你非常体贴 还叫你不用这么客气的
they said it was very thoughtful, and totally unnecessary.
但我要谢谢你，做的非常好 他们就喜欢别人送他们花
But off the record, well done, A plus, 'cause they love that sort of thing.
他们都很平易近人 你妹妹也很漂亮
Oh, they're lovely people. And your sister's very bright.
有时候脾气不好
Frighteningly so at times. But...
总而言之，她很喜欢你 她想邀请你到
Anyway, she thought you were terrific, and she wanted to invite you
我们的乡间别墅 和我的父母一起过周末
to our country house with the parents on Sunday.
那天会有个派对 有不少名人参加
'Oause they're having a party, there'll be some good people.
你还可以听到一些经典的音乐 因为我老爸是音乐收藏发烧友
And l'll play you some great music, because Dad's got an epic collection.
克洛伊 你想陪克里斯打会球吗
Ohlo Ohlo, do you wanna have a knock with Ohris for a bit?
现在已经5点了，亲爱的
lt's just that it's 5:00 somewhere, darling,
我要去调鸡尾酒了
and l've some serious cocktails to start making.
爱尔兰人 你喝过古巴ibre和caipirinha没
lrish! Have you ever had a Ouba libre or a caipirinha?
只和我打 克里斯会觉得无聊的
lt'd be really boring for Ohris to play with me on my own.
他陪我打也很无聊 但他打的不错
lt's really boring for him to play with me, but he's a good sport.
而且，他更喜欢和美女打球呢
And anyway, you've got better legs than l've got. Ohop chop.
别害怕 我以前还教连球拍都没拿过的人呢
Don't be silly. l teach people who have never held a racket before.
我真的很差劲 那你跟我学习
l'm so bad. that's how you get better.
就能变厉害点，来吧
Playing with a stronger player. Oome on.
好的
Ok.
我是不是很烂
Was l dreadful?
一点也不烂 你有与众不同的球风
Not at all. You have a very unique style.
是啊，笨拙的球风 对了，你怎么打得这么好
Yeah, it's called clumsy. How did you get to be so good anyway?
汤姆说你跟一些职业高手交过手
tom says you played with some of the real greats.
对我来说 那样只是为了摆脱贫困
For me, it was a way out of a poor existence.
想引起好教练的注意罢了
Oaught the eye of a good coach. l don't know.
刚开始还挺容易的
lt all came so easy at first.
你喜欢教人练球吗 并不尽然
Do you enjoy teaching? Not really.
我是说，还好吧
l mean, it's Ok for now,
不过如果要我当一辈子教练的话 就没意思了
but l'd cut my throat if l thought l had to do it forever.
我希望可以做些其他的
l'd like to do something with my life.
有意义一点的 我希望能够出人头地
You know, special. l'd like to make a contribution.
看来你是一个从爱尔兰来伦敦的 有志气的穷人
So, you're a poor boy from lreland come to London.
没错
l love it.
这里让人激情膨拜
lt's so exciting and alive.
我从没见过这么多的艺术品和歌剧院
l've never seen so much art or theater.
现在我可以好好欣赏了
Not that l've taken much advantage of it yet.
如果你想找人 带你到周围逛逛的话
Well, look, if you'd like someone to show you around,
我很乐意带你去些好地方逛逛 我从小在贝格维亚长大（上流住宅区）
l grew up in Belgravia. l'd be happy to take you to all the good places.
那太好了
that'd be great.
但得让我来买门票
On one condition: l buy the tickets.
没问题 那是命令吗
Oh, dear, is that going to be an issue?
我想是吧 我这人有点传统
l'm afraid it is. l'm very old fashioned.
我以前有看过
But actually, l did read something about the...
萨赤戏院展览会的一些资料
...exhibition in the Saatchi Gallery.
那里太棒了 我很乐意陪你去看看
that's perfect. lt'd be my pleasure to take you.
你愿意真是太好了
You're very kind to offer this.
我可以免费给你上几堂课作为补偿吗
Oan l at least give you some free tennis lessons?
好的，没问题
Ok, it's a deal.
星期三去怎么样
How about Wednesday for the Saatchi?
没问题
l can do that.
我们是不是先碰面吃过午饭再去 就这么说定了
Shall we meet for lunch first? lt's a date.
我想现在我最好先去洗刷一下 客人就要到了
l'd better get ready. Your guests will be arriving soon.
对..当然，去吧
Yeah, yeah. Of course. Go.
满头大汗的网球运动员 可不是他们现在想见到的
A sweaty tennis player's hardly what they expect.
谁会是我下一个手下败将
So who's my next victim?
你吗
You?
我很久没打乒乓球了
l haven't played table tennis in quite a while.
一千英镑一局怎么样
Would you like to play for a thousand pounds a game?
形势严峻啊
What did l walk into?
应该这样
lt's like this.
可以吗 请
May l? Please.
用球拍斜着击球
You have to lean in, and hit through the ball.
没见到你前我也是这么打的
l was doing just fine until you showed up.
假的不能再假了
the story of my life.
说说看
So, tell me,
一个美丽，年轻的美国乒乓球选手
what's a beautiful, young, American Ping Pong player doing
怎么会出现在英国的上流社会中
mingling amongst the British upper class?
有人跟你提过 你很自以为是吗
Did anyone ever tell you, you play a very aggressive game?
有人跟你提过 你有非常性感的嘴唇吗
Did anyone ever tell you you've very sensual lips?
极端自以为是 有一说一而已
Extremely aggressive. l'm naturally competitive.
那样说让你不高兴吗
ls it off putting?
我得想想看是不是
l'll have to think about that for a while.
原来你在这
there you are.
我给你介绍 这位是克里斯·维尔顿
l wanted to introduce you to Ohris Wilton.
克里斯·维尔顿 这是诺拉·赖斯，我未婚妻
Ohris Wilton, this is Nola Rice, my fiancee.
原来你就是那个网球教练
So, you're the tennis pro.
你好啊，亲爱的 很荣幸认识你
Hello, darling. My pleasure.
他刚才赢了我了
He was trying to have his way with me over the table.
哦，是吗 那你得留心了
Oh, really? Yeah, well, you'd better watch out for this one.
他可是靠这个混饭吃的
He's made a living out of hustling.
下一次我会有所准备的
l'll be ready for you next time.
我在外面等你 好
l'll see you outside. Oh, yeah.
有种很特别的气质，是吧
She's quite something, isn't she?
你们在一起多久了 六个月
How long have you been together? Six months.
天哪，才六个月
Jesus, yeah, six months!
她到伦敦学表演 我们在一个派对上认识
She came over to study acting, and l met her at a party
一见钟情，结果...
that l'd crashed and she'd crashed, and...
就订婚了
...one thing led to another.
事实上 我老妈很长时间都不能接受
Obviously, it's taken Mother quite a long time to get used to the idea
我对她那么认真这个事实
that l'm serious about her, but...
和你老实说吧
to be honest with you,
我妈经常私底下问我
Mother's always had this funny little agenda for me
是不是真的要和这个女演员结婚
which doesn't really involve marrying a struggling actress.
况且还是个美国人
Especially an American one.
但我实在太喜欢她了
But l am crazy about her.
说回来，我觉得我们下周可以一起去吃顿饭 你觉得怎么样
Anyway, l think we should all go to dinner next week. What do you think?
没问题 好极了
l'd love to. Excellent.
现在呢，爱尔兰人 晚饭前来点苏格兰酒怎么样
Now, lrish, how about a little drop of Scottish before supper?
不错 走撒，快点
Why not. Lead on. Quickly.
这几天下午我很开心
these afternoons have been great.
我很高兴你有这么多时间陪我
l'm so glad your schedule allows you so much time off.
是啊，很开心
Yes, it's fun.
多开几个小学生课程就补回来了
Although it wouldn't hurt to have a few more pupils.
你缺钱吗
Do you need money?
当然不
God, no.
不，不需要
No, l'm fine.
谢谢你的好意 但我真的不缺钱
lt's very sweet of you to ask, but l don't.
我这样问是因为我在乎你
l'm only asking because l care about you.
去你那还是去我那
Shall we go to your place or mine?
我想我家你一定不习惯
l don't think mine's quite what you're used to.
闭嘴，我想你家一定不错
Shut up. l think yours'll be just great.
我知道你最近常和克里斯·维尔顿在一起
You've been seeing a lot of Ohris Wilton lately, l understand.
是啊，他人不错 我喜欢他
Yeah. He's very nice. l liked him.
我只是不知道他的理想是什么
l just don't understand what he's aiming for.
他肯定不想一辈子都当网球教练
He certainly doesn't want to be a tennis pro for the rest of his life.
我也觉得他讨人喜欢
Well, l find him very likeable.
靠唯一的本事闯出生天 让人敬佩
He's fought his way up the only way open to him, and he's not trivial.
我和他有过非常愉快的谈话
l had a very interesting conversation the other day about Dostoyevsky.
我们能不能帮帮他
Oan't we do something for him?
在你的公司给他个职位什么的
A place in one of your companies or something?
他要你这样说的吗
Has he expressed a desire?
不是，但是，他很关心自己的前途 你知道的
No, but... he's open, you know, about his future.
他很想出人头地
He really wants to make something of his life.
克洛伊, 小心点
Ohloe, be careful.
汤姆已经和那个我不喜欢的女人搞的昏天暗地了 你不要也这样
tom's involved with a woman l have reservations about. Don't rush off.
汤姆和诺拉在一起很开心 你不喜欢她只是因为她是美国人
tom's happy with Nola. You're prejudiced 'cause she's American.
她被宠坏了 而且喜怒无常
She's spoilt and temperamental.
她是演员，情绪化很正常
She's an actress, they're emotional.
她对前途一片茫然, 而且喜怒无常 根本不适合汤姆
She's deluding herself, and she's moody. She's not right for tom.
反正我很喜欢克里斯 而且我想他对我也有一样的感觉
Well, l care very deeply for Ohris, and l think he feels the same way.
你们到底在说谁啊 诺拉
Who are you talking about? Nola.
是不是等了很久了 没有
Have you been waiting ages? Hello. Not at all.
交通太糟糕了 他们俩还得等会才到
traffic was awful. the others'll be here in a minute.
可能在哪里塞车了
they're probably stuck in it somewhere.
给我一杯香槟鸡尾酒，谢谢
Oan l have a champagne cocktail, please?
你爸爸的一个同事今天找过我 谈了一些工作的事情
One of your father's associates spoke to me today about the possibility of a job.
你是不是和你爸说了什么
Did you say anything?
我只是叫老爸留意一下 如果有什么好点的职位
Look, l just told Papa to keep his eyes open if anything juicy opened up,
可以优先让你试试 如果你喜欢的话
so you could have first option, if you wanted it.
你不想这样, 是吗 当然不
You're not cross, are you? God, no.
你对我真是太体贴了
lt's extremely thoughtful of you.
谢谢
thanks.
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
我得好好考虑一下
l'm gonna have to think about it.
我从来没做过生意
l've never really seen myself in the business world.
那你对自己的未来怎么看
So, what do you see for yourself, you know, in the future?
我不知道，真的
l don't know, really.
我是说 我知道这是一个很好的机遇
l mean, l'm sure it's a great opportunity.
本来就是
l think it is.
爸爸说这是一个学习做生意的好机会
Papa said it's a chance to learn the business.
如果你做的好 他会知道的
And if things go well, he'll see to it, you know, that...
你会提升的很快
...you move up quickly, or whatever.
我对办公室工作没多少感觉
l've always felt so so about office work.
这不完全是办公室工作
lt's not exactly office work.
把它想象成阶梯要好点
think of it more as a stepping stone.
到哪里
to?
到一个更重要，更多责任
to a biggerjob, more responsibility,
更高收入的职位什么的
greater earning potential, l don't know.
你不是一直说 你很敬佩我爸爸的造诣的吗
You've always said how much you admire Papa's accomplishments.
当然
Of course.
我是说，这有点奇怪 我知道那么多的人
l mean, it's strange, but coming where l come from,
但我就只敬佩你爸爸这样的人
l've always admired men like your father.
富有但不乏味
Wealthy, but not stuffy.
创造财富的同时
Enjoying his fortune.
还喜欢欣赏艺术
Having a grand time, supporting the arts.
说真的，他真的想帮帮你
Well, he'd really like to open some doors for you, that's all.
他还是个慷慨的人
He's a very generous man.
他欣赏你有上进心和反对不平等
He respects how you've pulled yourself up, against the odds.
你看上去不是很感兴趣 对不起
You don't seem very enthusiastic. l'm sorry.
我希望我的犹豫没有让你不开心
l hope my hesitation isn't upsetting.
不，不，一点都不 是应该考虑考虑的
No, no, not at all. lt's just that, you know,
你总是在说想出人头地...对不起
you've always talked about making a contribution and... l'm sorry.
我会的，我保证
l will. l promise.
哦，来了 好啊
Oh, good. Hello.
你们好，伙计们
Hi, guys.
你好
Hello.
交通真是太糟糕了
Don't worry, the traffic was awful.
我的错 我把诺拉拉去看车展了
lt's my fault, l dragged Nola to the classic car show at ExOeL.
是吗 难以置信
Really? lt was unbelievable.
我发誓 我的裤子差不多干了
l swear, my trousers have barely dried.
哦，天啊，闭嘴
Oh, God. Shut up.
你也喜欢车，是吗 克里斯
You love your cars, don't you, Ohris?
我觉得老式车好看一点 我也比较喜欢老式车
l think the old ones are beautiful. Yeah, l like the old ones.
但汤姆喜欢那些新款的 带些小饰物的那种
But tom likes all those new ones with the gadgets and...
我想要一辆阿斯顿马丁车
l want an Aston Martin.
我开过阿斯顿马丁 真的吗
l drove an Aston Martin. Really?
是的，以前我替一个人做事 经常帮他洗车
Yeah, l used to work for a man, and l used to wash his cars for him.
他非常非常溺爱 谢谢
He was very, very particular about thank you.
他的车所以我不得不每天都要用牙刷来洗
taking care of them, so l had to wash them every day with a toothbrush.
我想要一辆阿斯顿马丁车 或者老式的敞蓬车
l want an Aston Martin, or one of those vintage convertible Mercedes.
没问题，等我们结婚后 我们就开始收藏老式车
Well, when we're married we'll collect vintage cars.
只要给我一辆破DB9车就行了 好吗
Just as long as l can have a DB9 with all the trimmings. Ok?
实际上 海德雷对收藏车最在行了
ln fact, Hedley is perfect for keeping all those cars.
说起海德雷 我们是不是该点菜了，他在等了
ln fact, speaking of Hedley... Should we order, 'cause he's waiting.
真不好意思 我要一份烤马铃薯拌蘑菇
Frightfully sorry. l'll have the baked potato with truffles.
那太好吃了 我也要那种
that'll be lovely. Yum yum. l'd like the same, please.
要不要来些前点
Nothing to start?
我看看酒单再说
Oh, l think the wine list.
我要一份俄式鱼子酱薄煎饼 谢谢
l'll have the caviar blinis, please.
我要烤鸡吧 不是吧
Roast chicken. God, boring!
跟你说吧 他们这里的俄式鱼子酱薄煎饼很不错
Honestly, they have the greatest caviar blinis here.
你应该尝尝 无所谓了
You should try them. that's Ok.
别，你喜欢鱼子酱吗 一般般
No, do you like caviar? So so.
一般般
'So so.'
真不好意思 他从小就被教育的不尝试新菜品
He's been brought up as a good boy, to always order modestly. l'm very sorry.
给他份薄煎饼吧
He'll have the blinis.
天啊 你老爸在礼节上对你很严厉吗
My goodness, was your father an oil rigger who specialized in etiquette?
他是有点严厉
He was kind of austere.
克里斯的爸爸是一个虔诚的信徒
Ohris's dad was a bit of a religious fanatic.
哦，不可思异
Oh, Ohrist.
他失掉两条腿后 就开始信奉耶稣了
After he lost both his legs, he found Jesus.
天啊，对不起 但看上去这交易划不来
God. Sorry, but itjust doesn't seem like a fair trade.
刚才你在说海德雷什么
What were you saying about Hedley?
爸爸邀请我们一起去狩猎 真的吗
Papa's invited us for some shooting. Oh, really?
我最好换一套衣服再去
l'd better bring a different change of clothes.
我想你妈妈不喜欢 我上次去时穿的衣服
l don't think your mother appreciated what l brought last time.
我想是因为你的泳衣 她更喜欢针织品
l think that was your swimsuit. She's used to slightly more fabric.
我肯定如果她知道你在电影里面穿针织品的话 她对你会改观的
l'm sure if she knew you'd worn it in a movie, she'd suddenly find it chic.
确实 你拍过很多电影吗
true. Have you done many movies?
只是一些商业广告 不是电影
lt was a commercial, not a movie.
但你从没有放弃拍电影的梦想
But your eyes went straight to her, if you know what l mean.
我的事业并不像计划的那样发展
l don't think my career has... really gone as planned.
你只是需要喘口气
Oh, you just need a break.
我觉得运气也很重要
l think it's important to be lucky in anything.
我不相信运气 我相信实干
Well, l don't believe in luck. l believe in hard work.
实干是必须的
Oh, hard work is mandatory,
但我想所有人都不能否认运气的存在
but l think everybody's afraid to admit what a big part luck plays.
科学家都越来越确认
l mean, it seems scientists are...
偶然运气的存在
...confirming more and more that all existence is here by blind chance.
没什么目的, 突然就出现了
No purpose, no design.
我才不管这个 随缘吧
Well, l don't care, l love every minute of it.
我正羡慕你这一点
And l envy you for it.
牧师经常说的 是什么来着
What was it the... the vicar used to say?
'绝望是反抗的源动力'
'Despair is the path of least resistance.'
老生常谈了，不是吗 有点意思吧
lt was something odd, wasn't it? lt was very strange...
我认为信念才是反抗的源动力
l think that faith is the path of least resistance.
哦, 天哪 哦, 天哪
Oh, God. Oh, God.
我们不能换个话题吗
Oan we change the subject, please?
诺拉不是在说表演的事吗 那个更有意思一点
Nola was talking about acting, which is much more interesting.
不，我只是说
No, l was...
我对自己的演艺有了另外一种看法
...just saying that l think l'm giving acting a second thought.
受不了家乡的人认为我失败了
l just can't bear people in my hometown to think l've failed.
现在我永远都不想再回到科罗拉多州去了
Not that l'm ever going back to Oolorado.
永远
Ever.
你选好酒了吗
Have you decided on a wine?
两瓶Puligny Montrachet（酒名） 谢谢
two bottles of Puligny Montrachet. thank you.
早上好，我是克里斯·威尔顿 罗德·卡瓦
Good morning. Ohris Wilton. Rod Oarver.
上午好，克里斯·维尔顿 罗德·卡沃
很高兴见到你 很高兴见到你
Good to meet you. Good to meet you.
你跟着艾伦·辛克莱办事
You'll be working under Alan Sinclair here.
艾伦，你好
Hi, Alan. How are you?
刚开始 你可能会觉得分配工作没有什么挑战性
At first, you may find the assignments a little unchallenging,
但很快你就会发现 这里情况变化很快
but that'll soon change as you appreciate how things wash here.
上班时间是朝九晚五 好的
lt's basically nine to five. Yes, yes.
所以你还是有很多时间打网球的 如果你想的话
So you'll have plenty of time to keep up the backhand, if you like.
如果你已经安顿好了的话
Now, if you're Ok with the package,
这个月初就开始上班吧
we'd like to begin the first of the month.
我肯定薪水不是问题
l'm sure the salary won't be a problem.
很高兴认识你, 艾伦 很高兴认识你
Good to meet you, Alan. Good. And you.
还有你，罗德
And Rod.
在这里你会过的很愉快 我相信我会
l'm sure you'll be happy here. l'm sure l will.
前途无量 谢谢
Exciting things are happening. Ok.
你得到那份工作 你不知道我有多开心
l can't tell you how happy l am you've taken thatjob.
实在太令人激动了
lt's such good news.
给 我买了这个送给你作为庆祝
Here, l brought you this to celebrate.
喔，谢谢
Wow. thank you.
照我看 你很快就能获得提升
Believe me, in no time you'll be running that division.
你比艾伦·辛克莱能干多了 虽然他也挺能干
You're so much more on the ball than Alan Sinclair. He's nice, but...
但他不够上进 这种唱片很稀有
...uninspiring. lt's very rare.
上面有一些优美的独唱曲
lt has some beautiful arias on it.
而且他的声音唱出了
And his voice expresses
生活中所有悲惨的事情
everything that's tragic about life.
你喜欢悲剧，是吗 你呢
You find it tragic, do you? And you?
我喜欢它
l love it.
让我们在家共进晚餐 顺便听听悲剧
Let's stay at home and have dinner, and listen to the tragedy.
我去开瓶酒给你
l'm gonna open one of those bottles of wine l got you.
Puligny Montrachet（酒名）
Puligny Montrachet.
汤姆下订前我从没听说过这种酒
l never heard of it before tom ordered it.
现在我却爱上它了
Now l'm addicted.
汤姆和诺拉请我们今晚一起去看电影
tom and Nola invited us to go and see a film with them tonight,
但我已经和他们说我们今晚没时间了
but l told them we're busy.
我们没什么节目啊
But we have no plans.
没什么特别要做的事情
Well, no special plans.
我以为我们说好了留在家里的
l thought we said we'd stay in?
是啊，不过我们可以改啊
Yeah, but it wasn't written in stone.
我们应该和他们一起去的
We could've joined them.
现在也可以啊 如果你喜欢的话
We still can, if you'd prefer it.
这不是喜不喜欢的问题 只是
lt's... it's not a case of preferring it, it's just...
和他们一起总是很开心 而且你喜欢看电影
...we always have fun with them, and you love films.
那现在要打给他们吗
Well, shall l call them?
我是说，当然 除非你不想去
l mean, sure, unless you'd rather not.
其实
Well...
就我们两个可能更有意思
lt might be more fun, just the two of us.
有酒有歌剧
the wine, the opera.
当然
Absolutely.
我只是觉得
l just figured...
二人世界什么时候都可以过
We can stay in any... any night, and...
而他们难得请我们看电影
...they're free and suggested a film.
什么电影
What's the film?
我不知道 但如果你想去
l don't know, but if you'd prefer it.
我想去看电影
l am in the mood for a film.
非常感谢，伙计
thank you so much, fella.
等一下，门打不开 可以了
Hello. Oh, hang on, l'm having problems with the door. there we go.
嗨, 伙计们 等一下
Hello, sweetie. Hi, guys. One second.
给你，伙计 非常感谢
there you go, fella. thanks so much.
愿考文垂队好运 对啊
Good luck with the Sky Blues. Oh, yeah, cheers.
诺拉呢
Where is she?
诺拉得了偏头痛 今晚来不了了
Nola got a migraine at the last moment, and unfortunately she can't make it.
她没事吧 我帮她带了问候
Oh, no. ls she gonna be all right? But she sends her love.
没事，过几天就好了
Yeah, she's gonna be fine.
看电影喽，《摩托车上的日记》 我敢打赌是她选的电影
Hell with her, Motorcycle Diaries! l bet that was her choice.
你怎么可能会想看这种电影
l can't believe this is what you really want to see.
你工作的同事都很喜欢你
Everybody likes you at work.
爸爸说他听到了一个好消息
Papa says he's heard great things.
你同事说你是个聪明的孩子
You're a very clever boy.
嘿
Hey!
Hey.
嗨 你好啊
Hi. How are you?
你在这里做什么 刚买了件毛线杉
What are you doing here? l was just looking for a sweater.
就汤姆穿的那种 是不是开士米绒
the kind tom has. ls it cashmere?
是羊绒
lt's vicuna.
羊绒 羊绒?
vicuna. vicuna?
对 哦
Yeah. Right.
你去哪
Where are you going?
有一点紧张
Oh, l'm just having a nervous breakdown.
为什么
Why? So...
10分钟后我有个试镜
Well, l have an audition in ten minutes and...
以前的话，我的信心一般都有10 现在却只有0
As usual, my confidence level, which started off at a ten, is now at a zero.
别担心，你会做得很好的 承你贵言，我要迟到了
Don't worry, you'll be great. Yeah. l'm gonna be late, so...
你想走走吗 是的，当然
Are you walk...? You wanna walk? Yeah, sure.
我的经纪人本来要陪我去的 但他取消了
My agent was supposed to meet me, but he canceled.
搞得我一团糟 我一个人去
So that's... awful. l'm alone to...
你想我陪你去 作为精神上的支持吗
Would you like me to come along for moral support?
那太好了，如果 好的
Yes. that would be great. lf you... Sure.
不影响你的话 没问题
lf it's not a problem. lt's not a problem.
没问题 那好
No, it's not a problem. Ok.
以前大型网球比赛前 我都会很紧张
l used to get really tense before big tennis matches.
你有试过瑜珈吗
Have you ever tried yoga?
没有 没有？
No. No?
嗨
Hi.
嗨 哦，嘿
Hello. Hi. Oh, hey.
怎么样 搞砸了
How was it? Blew that.
在家里做得来的 但是
ltjust works, you know, at home, but...
我不知道 试镜却没没一次
l don't know, l just can never really pull through...
最终成功过 你会的
...in the end. You will. You will.
希望吧
Yeah.
其实
You know what,
我现在很想去喝点酒让自己好受点
l could actually use a drink just to pull myself together...
就一点点 没问题
...a little bit. Sure.
好吧 这边吧
Ok. this way.
我说到哪了
What was l saying?
我妹妹去大学读了几年书
My sister went to college for a couple of years.
但我和你一样，靠自学
But l'm like you, l'm self taught.
你应该见见我妹妹的 她
You should see my sister, she's...
她非常的漂亮 但她迷上了毒品
...she's very beautiful, but she's lost in drugs and...
我肯定她没有你漂亮
l'm sure she's not more beautiful than you are.
我是性感美，但琳达
What l am is sexy. But Linda's...
我的妹妹
My sister...
是古典美
...is classically beautiful.
所以你知道你对男人的吸引力?
So, you are aware of your effect on men?
在我的父母离异前 他们经常带她去参加选美比赛
Before my parents split, they used to put her in these pageants.
说笑的
lt's just a joke.
你爸爸是做什么的
What did your father do?
他遗弃了我们
He... left.
从没寄过钱回来
And never sent any money.
而我的妈妈也没一份工作能做好
And my mother could never hold down a job.
没一份? 对
No? No.
她酗酒
Her problem was that she drank.
你怎么认识汤姆的
How did you meet tom?
在一个派对上
We met at a party.
他
He...
看见我后
...saw me across the room
就好象一个追踪导弹一样跟着我
and he honed in on me, like a guided missile.
而我
And l...
马上就爱上他了
l liked him right off, you know.
我想
l thought...
我觉得他真的很帅
Well, l think he's very handsome.
你不觉得吗
Don't you?
是很帅
very.
他向你求婚了吗
And he asked you to marry him?
他
Well, he...
送了很多礼物给我
...swept me off of my feet with presents and, you know...
我怎么知道那是什么样的生活
What did l know about that kind of life?
我只是一个来自科罗拉多的穷演员
l'm just a starving actress from Boulder, Oolorado.
除此外
But...
我曾经有一段不如意的婚姻 这也是她不喜欢我的原因
l had another bad marriage behind me. that's another reason she hates me.
谁 埃莉诺，汤姆的妈妈
Who? Eleanor. tom's mother.
她想他娶一个叫奥利维亚的女孩
She wants him to marry this girl named Olivia,
好像是他的远亲 我不知道，我觉得有点恶心
who l think is a distant cousin. l don't know. lt's... it's sick.
肥水不流外人田的家庭
lt's such an inbred family. lt's...
你们是一见钟情吗
And was it love at first sight for you too?
我觉得他很帅
l thought he was very handsome.
我刚才提过了，我只是
You know, and l told you l was just...
完全被他俘虏了
l was overwhelmed with attention.
说说你和克洛依吧
So, what about you and Ohloe?
她很可爱
She's very sweet.
She is very sweet.
她想嫁给你
And she wants to marry you.
我想她的妈妈也不会同意的
l don't think her mother would approve of that either.
不，不，这不一样
No. No, it's different.
埃莉诺不买我的帐 但你肯定是
l don't buy into Eleanor, and she knows it, but you...
准新郎
...are being groomed.
我不会看错的
You mark my words.
上一次当他们以为 克洛伊跟一个穷小子私奔的时候
they almost died when they thought that Ohloe had run off with some...
他们差点没熬过来
...guy that ran a gastropub in the city.
但
But...
你有很好的前途 除非你自己搞砸了
You're gonna do very well for yourself, unless you blow it.
我会怎样搞砸呢
And how am l going to blow it?
比如跟我调情
By making a pass at me.
是什么让你觉得会是那样的
And what makes you think that's gonna happen?
男人都很好奇
Men always seem to wonder.
他们以为我与众不同
they think l'd be something very special.
你是吗
And are you?
至少没人要求退钱
Well, no one's ever asked for their money back.
刚才试镜时不见你如此自信
Where was all this confidence when you needed it in the audition?
我喝的太多了
l've had too much to drink.
能帮我叫辆计程车吗
Oan you get me a cab?
当然可以
Sure.
谢谢
thank you.
你是不是开的有点快
You were driving a bit fast,
是吗 早上好
weren't you? Good morning.
它在哪 第二格
Which one is he in? Second one over there.
哦，嗨
Oh, hi.
你觉得它会好起来来吗
So, do you think he's gonna be all right?
卡米克上周来看过它了
Oarmichael came and had a look at him the other week.
他太好了
Oh, he's so sweet.
右后腿有点问题
the problem with the right hind is gonna...
差点就被切掉了
lt should have dissipated fully already.
汤姆, 我可以喂它吗 可以，喂它点干草吧
tom, can l feed him? Yeah, yeah, wack him some hay.
汤姆, 你觉得它周日能参赛吗
tom, do you think he's gonna be able to play on Sunday?
它可以参赛 但问题是
Well, he will play on Sunday, but it's just the problem with the fact
只有洛佩斯能够驯服它 而洛佩斯受了伤
that it's only Lopez who can ride him, and he's injured at the moment.
我们被伤病拖后腿了
We're having a bloody nightmare with injuries.
你太美了
You're so beautiful.
公司准备付钱 让你到学校去修读一个商业课程
What would you say to the idea of taking a business course at school
你觉得怎么样
that the company would pay for?
我不知道
l don't know.
你前期的工作 反馈非常不错
l've had very good feedback on your work.
明年年初
And the beginning of next year
公司准备增设一些高级职位
there's going to be a very significant position opening up.
高职责，高薪水
One that carries a great deal of responsibility and pays accordingly.
附带一些福利
Plus, there are a number of perks...
报销开支啊，司机啊等等
Expense account, driver, et cetera.
我们正在关注适合此职位的人
We had been focusing on someone else...
虽然你和克洛伊很亲近
...but it's obvious to me that you and Ohloe have become close.
但如果你不符合条件 我一样不会用你
Although l wouldn't consider it, if l didn't think you were qualified.
我不会让您失望的
l'd hate to disappoint you.
抱歉，来晚了 快点
Oh, excuse me. Oome on, Ohris...
我们都准备好了
We're nearly ready.
我准备了一支枪给克里斯 谢谢你, 汤姆
l'll bring a gun for Ohris. thanks, tom.
没关系，伙计
Never mind, fella.
松鸡成群的季节很快就到了
this is basically a tune up for the grouse season, which is starting soon.
马上就可以大屠杀了 别吓唬他
But it's bloody good fun. Don't frighten him.
他的射击可没网球好
His shooting's not really up to his tennis, poor thing.
我会把他训练成很好的松鸡猎手的
l'll make an accomplished grouse shooter of him yet.
不用担心, 克里斯 希望你可以，爸爸
Don't you worry, Ohris. Quite right, Papa.
到你了, 克洛伊
Oome on, Ohloe.
嗨，亲爱的
Hi, darling.
你看到我的书了吗
Have you seen my Strindberg book?
没有
No.
你的试镜怎么样了
How did your audition go?
恐怕非常的糟糕
Oh, it was pretty awful, l'm afraid.
她自己搞砸了，祝福她吧 她正在加强
lt's her own fault, bless her. She just tightens up.
我相信事情总会好起来的
Well, l'm sure something worthwhile will come along.
不幸的是 没有其他什么让我感兴趣
Unfortunately, there's just not anything right now that l'm that great for.
那么你还想坚持多久
So, how long do you keep it up?
多久?
How long?
如果花了那么多时间 而又没什么收获的话
Well, if time passes and nothing significant materializes,
在你决定去做其他的事前
how long do you keep on going before you decide that...?
你还想坚持多久
to try something else?
我不觉得诺拉到了那个地步，妈妈
l hardly think Nola's reached that point, Mother.
我没有说那个
l'm not saying that.
我说的是 你尝试演艺已经有一段时间了
All l'm saying is you give acting a try for a time,
如果还是这样没什么成绩 你就得问问自己
and if you keep being disappointed you have to ask yourself the question,
'我到底想要什么，这是我想要的吗'
'ls this really what l want in my life? ls this what l want?'
其实我有问过我自己
Well, l do ask myself that.
听到了吗，逻辑上要这样, 汤姆
See? lt's only logical, tom.
尤其是对女性来说
Especially for a woman.
对女性来说 这是特别残酷的事情
lt's a particularly cruel business for a woman,
当时光流逝，你渐渐变老
and as you get older and time passes,
如果年轻时没什么成绩的话 年老时就会变的越来越难
if nothing happens it gets harder and harder.
埃莉诺，诺拉还很年轻
Eleanor, Nola isn't exactly over the hill.
我又不是说现在
l'm not saying now.
我是一个勇于面对现实的人
But l'm a great one for facing up to realities.
你接受现实是你自己的观点 与朋人无关
Your take on these realities is your own opinion and nothing else.
坦白说 并不是所有人都愿意听你说这个
Frankly, not everybody else is interested in hearing about it.
汤姆, 别这样大声对你妈说话
tom, don't raise your voice to your mother, please.
我没有大声说话 对不起，爸爸
l'm not raising my voice. And l'm sorry, Papa,
但这是诺拉自己的事情 不要老是这样
but she's always on Nola's case, continually discouraging her via...
含沙射影
...innuendos.
我只是在说演艺很能迷惑人
All l'm saying is acting's so will o' the wisp.
试过的人就知道
those that have it, know it right off.
盲目追崇只是不想回到家
to pursue it because you don't want to admit defeat
向朋友承认失败 坦白说，演艺是不切实际的
to friends back home is, frankly, unrealistic.
很遗憾这样说 但我就是这样看问题的
l'm sorry, but that's the way l feel.
失陪了
Excuse me.
诺拉
Nola.
没事 我只是想自己静静
lt's Ok. l'd like to be alone, thanks.
拜你所赐 如果我大声说话了我表示遗憾
Well, thank you very much. And l'm sorry if l'm raising my voice now,
你明知道那是她的痛点的
but you know that's her Achilles heel, emotionally.
他说的对, 埃莉诺 你说的是有点过火了
He's right, Eleanor. l think you've had one too many G and t's.
我正想找你
l was looking for you.
我心情不好 想一个人静静
l was upset. l just wanted to be alone.
我无意干扰
l don't mean to intrude.
我想喝酒
l need a drink.
我喜欢你喝酒的样子 有点轻佻
l like you when you drink. You get flirtatious.
是吗 是的
Do l? Yeah.
我非常肯定 我觉得你跟到这来
Oonfident. l don't think this was a good idea.
并不是一个好主意
You shouldn't have followed me here.
你觉得心虚吗
Do you feel guilty?
你呢
Do you?
不能让别人知道
We can't do this.
我知道
l know.
这不能代表什么
this can't lead anyplace.
你好
Hello.
亲爱的，找你的
Darling, l think it's for you.
去外面听
But take it outside.
至少还有希望
Well, there's hope, at least.
什么时候会有回复
When's the callback?
你有消息就尽快通知我
Just let me know when you hear anything at all,
我真的觉得我很适合这个角色
'cause l really think l could be great in this part.
对，好
Yeah. Ok.
再见
Bye.
为什么你对我这么冷漠
Why have you been so cold to me?
没有啊 不，你有
l haven't been cold. Yes, you have.
自从我们从乡下别墅回来以后
Ever since we came back from the countryside
你就在疏远我，逃避我
you've been distant, evasive.
我不想助长什么
l don't want to encourage anything.
过去的已经过去了, 克里斯
What happened, happened, Ohris.
当时大家都不理智
l mean... the moment was very out of control for many reasons.
我心烦意乱，风雨又大
l was upset, l was drinking, and the storm was overpowering.
哦，别找借口了 我没找借口
Oh, stop rationalizing. l'm not rationalizing.
那只是一时冲动 我们都有自己的伴侣
Passions are passions, but we're both very involved with other people.
你别演戏了 不可能的
You're not such a good actress, you know. lt's not possible.
你老是在想我们做爱的事
Look, you daydreamed about making love to me,
我并不是说我没有想过
and l'm not saying the fantasy didn't cross my mind, Ok?
我们是待过
We had our moment.
但，生活还得继续 我们回到现实中来吧
But, you know, let's move on, get back to reality.
克里斯 我快要成为你的嫂子了
Ohris, we're gonna be brother and sister in law.
你口是心非
You were exactly as l pictured you'd be making love.
克里斯, 忘了吧 结束了
Ohris, forget it. lt's over.
谢谢 亨利
thanks. Henry!
嗨，你好吗 克里斯，还好
Hey. How are you? Ohris. All right.
看看你 见到你真高兴
Look at you. Good to see you.
混的还不错嘛
Looks like you're doing all right for yourself, aren't you?
谢谢 你还在打巡回赛吗
thanks. You still doing the tennis tour?
是啊, 乐此不疲 看看这车
Yeah, l love it. l love it. Look at this car.
不是我的 公司的车
Oh, don't worry, it's not mine. lt's the company's.
我知道你已经转行了
Yeah, l know you found it a bit of a grind, didn't you?
而我还在为比赛全球奔波
But l'm still circling the globe, deluding myself.
我受不了那样
l just couldn't stand it.
是啊 我听说你做起了生意
No. No, l heard you went into business.
只是办公室里跑腿的轮子而已 如果你信的话
l'm a wheel in an office, if you can believe it.
那也是只大轮子啊 原来你知道啊, 亨利
A big wheel. lt's who you know, Henry.
我攀上了一个女孩 人还不错
l got involved with a woman. very nice.
家里很有钱
Family's got nothing but money.
不动产，仆人，马球场 挺吸引人的
Big estate, servants, polo ponies. All quite lovely.
看的出来
Hey, look, l understand.
种子选手给你带来的心灵创伤 还没有消失殆尽啊
lt beats getting your heart broken all the time by the top seeds.
生活就像网球那样
lsn't it amazing how much of life turns on whether the ball
要么过网，要么弹回来 不是很神奇的事吗
goes over the net or comes right back at you?
我一直很佩服你的球技
l always admired your game though, you know?
谢谢 你发挥很稳定
thanks. You were very steady.
沉着冷静，还富有创造性
Oool under pressure, but creative.
你完全可以有拉雷罗那样的造诣
You could be a poet with the racket like Laver was.
我跟你也只不过半斤八两
l lost to you as much as l beat you.
不，你和我打的时候 只是输给了自己
No. When l played you, you never beat yourself.
我跟你说吧 如果你没改行
l'm telling you, a couple of bounces the other way,
你可能已经打败一些种子选手了
you might've beaten some of those top seeds.
我能请你吃午饭吗
Listen, can l buy you lunch?
要不我下次进城的时候吧
that's... What about next time l'm in town?
把你电话给我 当然
Give me your number. Oertainly.
我可能要搬到新公寓 这是我的名片
l'm moving into a new flat, so this is my business card.
随时都可以打给我 没问题
You should call me anytime. very impressive.
很高兴见到你，亨利
So good to see you, Henry.
你看起来不错 你也不错啊
You look well. And you, mate.
是非常非常不错 我请你吃午饭吧
You look very, very well. l can buy us lunch.
把帐报到卡上就行了 好
Put it on the expense account, so... very well.
记得打给我 没问题
...do call. very good. Yeah, yeah.
走了 再见
All right. Bye.
哦，我的天啊 就在那
Oh, my God. Right there.
她还戴了眼镜 为什么
She's got glasses on. But why on earth...?
为什么你妈要请她来这里
Why on earth would your mother invite her here?
她昨天在超级市场遇见她 就邀请她了
She met her at the supermarket yesterday and invited her...
超级市场? 没错
the supermarket? Yes.
你会弹钢琴吗 不会，我最怕钢琴了
Oan you play the piano? No, l'm terrible at the piano.
你们什么时候结婚 妈咪
So, when are you two getting married? Mummy!
得了吧, 埃莉诺 哦，别那么吃惊
Oh, gosh, Eleanor! Oh, don't look so surprised.
别说了
Stop it.
你们交往已经有一段时间了
You've been like two peas in a pod for a long time now.
不要告诉我还没说到正题
Don't tell me the subject hasn't come up.
妈咪, 跟我来
Mummy, come with me. Oh, dear.
你需要一杯浓咖啡，快点
You need a strong cup of coffee. Oome on.
埃莉诺喝多了就有一些神经质
Eleanor doesn't hold back when she's had a few.
其实也没什么 克洛伊和我也商量过了
Look, it's a reasonable question. Ohloe and l have discussed it.
我和埃莉诺都非常高兴你加入这个家庭
Eleanor and l would be delighted to welcome you to the family.
汤姆也很希望你成为他妹夫
tom would love having you as a brother in law,
你们俩有什么需要尽管说
and whatever you two need, you can always rely on us.
非常感谢
l appreciate that.
亲爱的，等一下
Darling, one second. l just think we...
你全看到了, 是不是 我肯定你看到了
You two have met, haven't you? l'm sure you've met.
不好意思，别介意
l'm sorry. Who'd have thought?
至于我们躲在这里
What, that we were hiding in the pantry?
都是她的鬼主意
lt was all her fault, you know.
她性欲来了我还能怎么办
Like, how can l help it if she gets turned on by sexual intimacy
我们也没有想到这里会被发现
in places that we know we're gonna get caught?
说谎 这个危险的游戏可是你的主意
You were... You! the risky business was your idea.
谁见到你都想占有你
All men who see you want to attack you.
对吗，克里斯
lsn't that right, Ohristopher?
哦，你没事吧
Oh, God, are you all right?
我很好
l'm fine.
我不应该空腹喝酒的
l shouldn't drink on an empty stomach.
我现在宣布你们成为夫妻
l now pronounce you man and wife.
你可以亲新娘了
You may kiss the bride.
哦，天哪
Oh, my God.
难以置信 是吗
this is incredible. lsn't it?
上面是什么 卧室
What's up here? that's the bedroom.
那里还有一个卧室
there's another bedroom through there.
浴室和厨房
the bathroom and a kitchen.
小阳台 喔
Little terrace. Wow.
看看这边的风景吧 太美丽了
But look at this view. Oh, it's breathtaking.
我希望我供得起 别再提出那个了
l just... wish l could afford it. Oh, don't bring that up again.
你知道爸爸会帮助我们的
You know it gives Papa pleasure to help.
快看 明媚光亮
Oome on. the light coming through every day.
很漂亮，但也太大了
lt's beautiful. But it's huge!
我在这里会迷路的
l'm gonna get lost in here or something.
我跟你说过我有恐高症吗 不是吧
Did l tell you l'm scared of heights? Really?
真的 那会是个问题
Yeah. that could be a problem.
我想你使我怀孕
l want you to make me pregnant.
克洛伊，我们说过了
Ohloe... We discussed this.
很快就会有的
lt's very quick.
怎么可能 我们都好久没一起睡了
lt's not quick, we've been sleeping together for ages.
我想生三个小孩 在我年轻的时候
And l want three children, and l want them when l'm young.
说定了，你行的 你有很强的能力
Oome on, you can do it, you've got a powerful serve.
嘿，你怎么了
Hey! Where are you?
我的错，对不起
l know, l know. l'm sorry.
没状态
Not good.
我想跟你说些事
Listen, l've got to tell you something.
什么
What?
我和诺拉
Well, Nola and l...
分手了
...broke up.
不是吧 真的
No! Yeah.
是我提出来的
Or, l should say, l called it off.
我还以为你们会结婚的
l thought you were gonna get married.
是啊 很难才开的口
Yeah, well, it's rather embarrassing to say
我妈妈只是不喜欢她
but l think Mother rather poisoned the well on that one.
这和我跟不跟奥利维亚结婚
Not that l have any intention in marrying Olivia sodding Allred,
没什么关系
who's her main candidate.
不可思议
God, no.
对不起，我只是不明白
l'm sorry. l don't understand.
我说的都是真的 没半点假
l suppose the whole truth, nothing but the truth,
现在的情形是
so help me God, part of the situation is, is that...
我和别人约会了
...l've met someone else.
不是吧 真的
No! Yeah.
我以前认识了一个女孩 我现在才知道我爱上了她
l met someone and l fell in love, and l just knew right away.
而且我妈妈也喜欢她
Although the fact that my mother is in seventh heaven about her,
我不停地跟自己说 和诺拉分手没什么，但
l keep trying to tell myself isn't a factor, but...
你知道我意思的
You know what l mean.
你拨的号码是空号
the number you are calling is not available.
不好意思
Excuse me.
你是找赖斯小姐吗 是的
Are you looking for Miss Rice? Yes.
她昨天搬走了 没住这公寓了
She's gone. Saw her yesterday. She's given up the apartment.
她有说搬去哪里吗 没有
Did she say where? Not to me.
谢谢 不客气
thanks. that's all right.
你在想什么 没什么
What are you thinking about? Nothing.
工作的事
Just business.
我们已经一个星期没有做爱了
You know it's been over a week since we made love.
哦, 克洛伊, 我很累
Oh, Ohloe, l'm beat.
你厌恶我了吗 当然不是
Am l being rejected? Of course not.
好吧，我可以等
Ok, l can take a hint.
我不知道是哪里出问题了 我的堂姐们怀孕都很容易的
Meanwhile, l don't know what's wrong. All my cousins get pregnant so easily.
听着
Look...
你会怀上的
...it'll happen.
我只是累了
l'm just really tired.
亲一个
kiss.
晚安
Sweet dreams.
现在我宣布你们成为夫妻
l now pronounce you man and wife.
你可以亲新娘了
You may kiss the bride.
正是时候 我已经准备好炫耀了
Just in time. l'm almost starting to show.
你得去看一下妇科医生
Well, you have to see a fertility doctor.
看过了
l know.
我们什么都试过了 这个怎么样
We've tried everything. What about this?
他的线条好鲜艳，不是吗
His brushstrokes are really intense, aren't they?
是啊，我不喜欢 是啊
Yeah, l don't like it. No.
你考虑过领养一个吗 不，绝对不
Would you ever consider adopting? No, absolutely not.
我想要自己的孩子
l want my own children.
这张呢
this one?
有一点
Sort of...
我有跟你说维多利亚怀孕了吗
Did l tell you victoria Phyfe is pregnant?
是吗
Really?
她很开心 喔
She's so happy. Whoa.
她和他的丈夫很恩爱
Her and her husband just found each other.
他们的婚姻很美满
All their neuroses intertwine so perfectly,
他们好象是上天注定的
and itjust works like a charm.
在她结束一切不开心的关系后不久 在一场交通事故中认识了他
After all their unhappy relationships, they met during a traffic accident.
不可思议 是啊，很棒
God... l know, it's great.
现在我们的律师正在办理
Well, our lawyers are going over it as we speak.
最迟星期五你就可以拿到初稿
You'll have a daft by Friday. l promise.
如果时间不够 我会熬夜搞定的
lf l have to work all night.
好的
Ok.
谢谢
thank you. thanks.
萨曼塔 麻烦给我两片阿斯匹林
Samantha, can l have two aspirin, please?
谢谢
thanks.
你还好吗，先生
Are you Ok, sir?
跟我说说，萨曼塔 你有觉得这里压抑吗
tell me, Samantha, do you ever feel claustrophobic in here?
没有，没有啊
No, not really.
哦，天哪
Oh, Ohrist!
我得去现代塔特见我妻子
l've got to meet my wife at the tate Modern.
那里有个画家 她想我看看他的作品
there's a new painter she wants to show me.
萨曼塔，如果他们回电话 告诉他们周五
lf they call back, Samantha, tell them Friday.
别提前
Not before.
再见
Good night.
克里斯 我正在找你
Ohris. Oh, l was looking for you.
你好，卡萝 你好, 克里斯
Hi, Oarol. Hi, Ohris.
怎么样, 亲爱的 棒极了
How are you, darling? Good.
基本上伟大艺术家的作品 他们都有展出
they've got the most amazing new artists here.
是吗
Yeah?
我想你看看这个女艺术家
l want you to see this woman from St. lves.
好的 你们待会要去哪
Oh, yes. Look, where are you going to be?
怎么了
Why?
我得去打个电话 这里一点信号都没有
l have to make a phone call, and l can't get any reception down here.
好吧，我们就在那边 你快一点，他们就要关门了
Well, we'll be over there. But hurry, 'cause they're closing soon.
很快
l'm coming.
好的
Ok. Ok.
你好啊
Hello.
惊讶吧
What a surprise.
我
l...
我搬回城里来了 我不知道你离开过
l moved back into town. l didn't know you'd left town.
分手的事让我很伤心
Yeah, l was really upset about everything that happened,
于是我回了美国 看能不能找份工作
so l just went back to America to look for a job.
我还以为你讨厌那里 任何地方除了这里
l thought you hated that place? Anyplace but here.
我找过你
l looked for you.
为什么
For what?
你还是很不开心
You're still so angry.
你住哪
Where are you living?
城里，怎么了
ln town. Why?
你一个人住吗
You live alone?
为什么要问这些问题 你不是结婚了吗
Why are you asking me these questions, aren't you still married?
我们去喝一杯怎么样
Oan l meet you for a drink?
聊聊天什么的
talk?
哪里能找到你，说吧
Where can l reach you? Oome on.
我的天哪，你好啊 嗨，亲爱的
My goodness. Hello. Hi, darling.
看我遇见谁了
Look who l bumped into.
你好 你好
Hi. Hi.
你好吗 很好，谢谢
How are you? l'm good. How are you?
你气色不错 谢谢
You look great. thanks.
汤姆怎么样 他很好
How's tom? He's fine.
真的很好 我听说他结婚了
Really well. Yeah, l heard he got married.
是的 他们有小孩了
Yeah. they've got a baby.
你知道汤姆的 一切都安定下来了
You know tom, all settled down.
我想我找到了 你们认识吗
Ok, l think l've found it. Do you two know each other?
这是我朋友卡萝 这位是诺拉
this is my friend Oarol. this is Nola.
你好 你好
Hi. Hi.
这个视频装置 我们找了很多地方了
We've been looking everywhere for this video installation.
现在才找到 不好意思
We can't find it at all. Will you excuse us?
我想在三楼，是吗
l think it's on the third floor, isn't it?
不 我想在那后面
Yeah. No, no, no. l think it's back there.
告诉我电话号码
Say your phone number.
你想做什么 告诉我就是了
What's the point? Just say your phone number.
克里斯 求你了
Ohris... Please.
告诉我电话号码
Say your phone number.
020 79460996
02079460996.
我会打给你的
l'll call you.
再见
Bye.
我想他医术不错
l think he really knows what he's doing.
你对他没好感吗
Didn't you get a good feeling about him?
对我来说 妇科医生只比巫医好一点
to me, fertility doctors are a cut above witch doctors.
他和上次那个不一样
Oh, yeah. Well, he's not like that last one.
不用了，约翰
lt's Ok, John.
我觉得这次会怀上的
l feel like it's gonna happen this time.
你先回去 我得去开会
You go ahead, l've got a few meetings.
我送你吧 不用了，就在这附近，走过去就行了
l'll drop you. No, it's Ok. lt's nearby. l'll walk.
好吧 家里见
Ok. See you at home.
再见
Bye.
你的公寓很不错啊
You have a very charming flat.
并没有像你上次说的那样被拆掉
the area's not as run down as you said it was.
运气不错 短时间内找到这样的房子
l was lucky to find it on such short notice.
只是觉得不够完美
l mean, it's not perfect.
这房子被盗好多次了
the building's been burglarized a couple of times and the...
住那边的那个女的家里犯鼠害
...woman down the hall has mice, but...
但大堂还是可以的
...you know, the lobby's decent.
关键是它便宜
the key word is it's cheap.
几点了
What time is it?
你该回去了
time for you to go.
真舍不得离开你
lt's so hard to leave you.
迷人的尤物
Beautiful woman.
睡得好吗
How'd you sleep?
不错
Good.
你昨晚有看新闻吗
God, did you see that stuff on the news last night
关于中国的地震
about that earthquake in Ohina?
惨不忍睹
terrible.
还有他们说的没完没了的
And there was this whole thing about how they've discovered
发现新行星的事 是吗
an entirely new planet. Yeah?
嗯
Yeah.
昨天我去了找合适新画廊的地方
l went looking for space to rent for the new gallery yesterday.
爸爸在这方面很支持
Papa's getting so into the idea.
相信对你有好处
lt should be good for you.
我得去上班了 是吗
l've got to go to work. Oh, really?
我在想我们是不是可以 你知道的
l was kind of hoping we might, you know...
在你上班之前
...before you went to work.
现在是排卵期 而且医生说了
lt's my time of the month, and remember the doctor said
我们要尽可能的在早上多做做
we really should try and do it as often as we possibly can in the morning.
亲爱的，我会迟到的 别这样，会很有意思的
Darling, l'm gonna be late. Oome on, it'll be fun.
等等，我要先量一下的体温
Wait, l've got to take my temperature first.
你想下周同一时间见面吗
So, you wanna meet the same time next week?
让我上去吧
Let me come up.
我们刚在旅馆消魂了一个多小时 不要告诉我你现在又...
We just spent an hour at the hotel. Don't tell me that you...
对不起，我情不自禁 你让我疯狂
l'm sorry. l can't help it. You drive me crazy.
你上班要迟到了 我才不管
You're gonna be late for work. l don't care.
快点
Oome on.
哦，艾斯比太太，你好 你好
Oh, Mrs. Eastby, hello. Oh, hello.
你的鼠害得到控制了吗
Hey, did you get that pest control...?
哦，当然
Oh, yes. Yes.
用一点花生酱就搞定了
the traps work better with a little peanut butter.
它比干酪好多了
lt's much better than cheese,
虽然大家都认为干酪是最好的
despite the popular notion that cheese is best.
这是哈里斯先生 下午好，你好
Oh, this is Mr. Harris. Good afternoon. How are you?
你好 很高兴认识你
Hello. Hello. Good to meet you.
待会见 再见
See you later. Bye bye.
再见
Bye.
我认为画廊座落在布鲁顿街的话 会很完美
But l think that Bruton Street would be perfect for the gallery
因为那里是商贸中心
because it's just right in the thick of things and...
人多的话效果自然好点
lt'll just be a natural success, l think,
而且你善于挑选油画和捣弄小古董
because you're great at picking out paintings and bric a brac.
是啊
Yeah.
希望开张的时候 我就可以怀上BB
knowing my luck, l'll get pregnant the minute it opens.
当然，你可以两者兼得的 我是说
Yeah, well, you can manage both. l mean...
黑德丝怀上罗丝的时候
Heths didn't have a problem
也没有什么问题
giving up Adair, when we first had Rosie.
当然，有很多人帮我们
Remember, we did have a lot of help though.
但是保姆后来走了 她在一部电影里找了个角色
But the nanny left us. She got a part in a movie.
不是吧 是的
No. Yeah.
你们知道我前几天碰见谁了吗
Actually, you know who we bumped into the other day?
你显然知道, 是诺拉
Obviously you know, but... Nola. Yeah.
我跟你说，我们也碰见过她 什么时候来着，就不久前
Well, l told you, we saw her. When was it? Ages ago now.
她现在在拉伯瑞街的一家专卖店上班
Yeah. Well, l think she's now working in a boutique on Ledbury Road.
我想那是保罗和乔的店
l think it's Paul and Joe's or something.
她居然还是单身
But she's just such an odd girl.
她看上去还是那么漂亮 抱歉，但事实是那样
l mean, she still looks great. Sorry, but it's true.
但有些只是...
But something's just...
感觉她和以前有些不一样 我只和她聊了两句
...changed in her face. l mean, l... We barely spoke.
汤姆说她看起来很辛苦的样子
tom said she looked a bit hard.
对的，她看上去 有点像做沙司的女人
Yeah, well, she's always, you know, been a lady of the sauce, so to speak.
但我认为这一点是世代相传的
And l think it kind of runs in the family,
怎么说呢
but, l don't know...
她看上去还是那么迷人
l mean she's still got that 'come hither' look.
她有男朋友吗 奇怪的是，我居然忘了问这个
ls she going out with anyone? Strangely, l forgot to ask.
我知道一定会告诉你的 卡洛伊
But l'll keep you in touch with that, Ohloe, let you know.
你好, 汤姆 你好
Hello, tom. Hello.
你怎么会在这里
Hello, fella. What are you doing here?
我们才过来不久 听说这里的意大利面很地道
We just popped in for a bit of, you know, local tagliatelle.
见到你太好了 多么温馨的家庭聚会啊
Good to see you. What a lovely family gathering.
你应该告诉我的 我们就可以来个六人组合了
You should have told us. We'd have made a sextet.
六人组合？ 下次就来个六人组合吧
A sextet. We could have had one of those.
你们下个月去海力？ 是啊，有此打算
You guys going to Hedley next month? Yeah, we're gonna try. Aren't we?
我知道汤姆很不想去
l know tom's dying to get away.
有一天我看见你了 叫你你没有听见
l was yelling at you the other day. You didn't hear me.
我?
Me?
是啊，你正在米堪宝街截计程车 5点的样子
Yeah, you were hailing a cab on Melcombe Street about, what, 5:00.
本想搭你一程的 有吗
l'd have given you a lift. l was?
米堪宝街在哪 不，不是我
Where's Melcombe Street? No, not me.
是你 我是说看上去和你一模一样
Yes, l mean it certainly looked like you.
米堪宝街在哪 不可能，我想你认错了
Where is Melcombe Street? No, l'm afraid you're mistaken.
认错人的事多如牛毛
But people are always taking me for other people. So...
我发誓就是你
l'd have sworn it was you.
克里斯不可能截计程车的
Well, it certainly wouldn't be Ohris hailing a cab.
他到哪都和司机一起的
He's completely dependant on our driver.
没错 不可能的
Quite right. very annoying.
你好好想想，你可能是忘记了 我肯定我没有认错人
You should check for early Alzheimer's. You're forgetting. l'm sure l'm right.
不, 你搞错了 不过还是谢谢你
No, you are mistaken. But thank you for thinking of me.
我觉得你们不是在胡扯
l think the only thing that comes out of this conversation is you're both nuts.
你知道我不会 就是喝多了，怎么可能
Well, you're an authority on that. Or drunk. How dare you?
我们得走了 打给我
Look, we'd better be going on. Look, call me.
没问题 享受你的晚餐吧
l will do. Enjoy your supper.
再见，后会有期 谢谢
Bye. See you. thanks.
疯子
Nuts.
下午好，玛丽亚
Good afternoon, lngrid.
萨曼塔, 下午有什么安排
Samantha, what do we have for this afternoon?
两点钟会见萨拉族人
Just the Sarazin people at two.
可以推迟一个小时吗 好的
Oan we push it an hour? Yeah.
我应该能赶回来，没有的话 好好招待他们
l should be back in time, but if l'm not, please make them comfortable.
克里斯，你去哪
Ohris. Where are you off to?
抱歉, 罗德 我得去应个约
l'm sorry, Rod, l've got an appointment.
下午要会见萨拉族人
We have Sarazin and company this afternoon.
我应该能赶回来，没有的话 不用等我
l should be back in time but if l'm not, please start without me.
是吗 没问题的，我有急事，真的
Really? lt's Ok. lt's important, trust me.
到我那去有点可笑
lt's ridiculous to go back to my place.
每次你去 都待不到一小时
Once we get there, you'll have less than an hour.
听着，并不是说和克洛伊一起不痛苦 只是
Look, it's not that l'm miserable with Ohloe, it's just...
我不想再谈论克洛伊
l don't wanna talk about Ohloe anymore!
我只是感到无聊 她人还是不坏的
Listen, it's just l'm bored! l mean, she's very nice, but...
克里斯 你心情不好吗
Ohris! Are you in a bad mood?
是的，我心情不好 我刚把一个试镜搞砸了
Yes, l am in a bad mood. l just blew another audition.
我厌倦了表演 永远都没有出路
l'm so sick of this acting thing, it's just not working out.
做演员并不容易
lt's a hard field.
你得不停的努力 我讨厌不停的试
You have to keep plugging at it. l'm sick of plugging.
汤姆的妈妈是对的 她说的一点都没错
tom's mother was right. ltjust gets to a point, you know?
也许我该称呼她为你岳母
Or should l say your mother in law?
我们不要说这些了好吗
Hey, look. Let's not go into one of those, Ok?
我不知道和你在一起为了什么 你从没想过要离开克洛伊
l don't know what l'm doing with you. You're never gonna leave Ohloe.
也许我会的
Maybe l will.
不要空口说白话
Don't say that unless you mean it.
克洛伊只是发了疯的想怀上孩子
Ohloe's just so desperate to get pregnant.
我们已没有激情可言
l mean, it's... mechanical.
没有你 我不知道我会怎样
l don't know what l'd do if l couldn't see you.
我是认真的
Really. l mean it.
圣诞快乐 调皮鬼
Merry bloody Ohristmas. Lovely.
你今天想抽几根烟
How many cigarettes are you gonna smoke today?
一百万, 至少 不要学抽烟
A million, at least. Please don't start smoking.
随他吧，今天是圣诞节 对身体不好
Well, it is Ohristmas. lt's such a pity.
别这样，只抽几支 你会变得...
Oome on, just a little one. lt's gonna...
你觉得没什么 其实不尽然
You think you're going to be living forever, you're not.
嗨
Hi.
祝你圣诞快乐
l wanted to wish you a merry Ohristmas.
我一直在想你
l've been thinking about you.
我明天可以离开一个小时左右
l may be able to get away tomorrow, for an hour or so.
好的，到时见
Ok. See you then.
再见
Bye bye.
你在这啊, 克里斯
there you are, Ohris.
克洛伊跟我说过去几个月
Ohloe tells me you've sustained some personal loss in the market
你在市场规划上犯了些错误
over the past few months.
我想我有点粗心了 精力 不够集中
Well, l guess l've been a little bit careless, not concentrating.
我认为我做了好的决定 没想到...
And, of course, l thought l made good decisions, but...
谁都想不到会这样
Well, who could have predicted these...?
我不想你和克洛伊担心什么
Look, l don't want you and Ohloe to worry.
我们会照看你的 你太好了，先生
You'll always have a safety net. You're too generous, sir.
你让克洛伊快乐
Oh, no, you've made Ohloe happy,
就是对我和埃莉诺最好的报答了
and that means a great deal to Eleanor and me.
我想这会是个令人向往的假期 是吗, 克里斯
Well, l think it's gonna be an amazing holiday. Don't you, Ohris?
当然
Yes.
我们可以选择在船上或者旅馆过夜
We have a choice of sleeping on the boat or in the different hotels.
船上 船上
Boat. Boat.
每晚都是 好极了，我也选船上
Every time. Good. l say the boat.
他从来没有去过希腊岛
Do you know he's never been to the Greek lslands.
什么 不是吧
What? No.
是的, 他从没去过
No, he's never been. You'll love it.
是的，我去过雅典 我听说那个岛简直就是个天堂
No. l have been to Athens, but l hear the lslands are paradise.
我想起来了
Oh, that reminds me,
我们可以去温斯顿和布鲁克的撒丁岛
we have to go to Sardinia to pop in on Brook and Dougie Winston.
不是吧 天哪
Oh, good. Oh, God.
那里房子很漂亮 布鲁克还行，温斯顿就免了吧
No, no, the house is beautiful. Brook's fine, Dougie's a nightmare.
听起来很浪漫 克利特岛
Sounds so romantic, doesn't it? Mkonos and Orete.
是啊 是的
Yeah. Yeah.
我很想快点见到 美丽古老的寺庙和剧院
l'm so anxious to see all the beautiful old temples and theaters.
天哪
Oh, God.
是啊 我可以和你一起去
Yeah. Oh, l'll do that with you. tom can stay...
我给克里斯买了 一个古老的希腊生育符咒
You know, l bought Ohris an ancient Greek fertility charm.
你还记得吗 永远也忘不了
Do you remember? l'll never forget.
我邮寄给他
l sent off for that fertility thingy.
叫他放在枕头下两个月
He had to put it under his pillow for two months.
当然什么也没发生
And absolutely nothing happened, of course.
太可惜了
Poor thing.
我把他整惨了 有人说他是个空枪王子
l'd just subjected him to the torture. they think he's firing blanks.
喂
Oh, shut up! Hello?
我想见你
l miss you.
笑一个，笑一个 不，一点都不好笑
Love me. Just love me. No, because it's not funny.
对不起
lt's not funny. l'm sorry.
我没法以身试之 所以言之不可信
Proof is in the pudding, and there ain't been any pudding.
我现在走不开 我不管
l can't get away right now. Well, you have to.
你什么时候能来
When can you get here?
明天，不 星期一
tomorrow. No, Monday.
听着
Look...
现在是三天假期的周末
lt's a three day weekend.
星期二吧
tuesday.
克里斯 我现在就得见到你
Ohris, l need to see you.
我看看能不能离开 待会再打给你
l'll see what l can do. l'll call you right back.
能见到芭芭拉·史翠珊太好了
l would love to meet Barbra Streisand.
她很友善 她和其他美国朋友一起来的
She's meant to be really lovely. She's with that other American fella.
是谁啊 我真是个笨蛋
Who was that? Oh, l'm such an idiot.
我忘记签一些文件了 可能要去城里一趟
l forgot to sign some papers. l may have to drive into town.
杰克·加纳
Jack Garner?
你不能去 银行都休假了
You can't go, it's a bank holiday weekend.
交通很烂的
the traffic'll be terrible.
我们都计划好了的
James Garner, that's it. l mean, we've all got plans.
不一定今天去
l don't mean today.
他们给自己的狗起名伊莲·佩姬
they named their little dog after Elaine Paige.
过几天再签肯定也没问题
Well, surely it can wait a couple of days.
他们为什么这么做？ 因为它晚上一直叫唤
Why did they do that? 'Oause it howls all night long.
我也这么觉得
Yes, l'm sure it can. Oh, that's mean.
同感，那是只很小的毛茸茸的狗
l know. And it's terribly small and furry.
太恶劣了
that's mean.
我想明天早上我们可以去骑骑马
l think tomorrow we should go for a morning ride.
我买了几匹新马
l've some lovely new horses.
你还记得克里斯第一次来这吗
Do you remember when Ohris came here first,
他不敢骑马
and he had some serious qualms about riding?
我跟泰德谈过 他怎么样？
l spoke to teddy. How is he?
今天上午他还在说想给自己买匹马呢
Well, this morning he was talking about buying a horse of his own.
不是吧 真的
No. Yeah.
我不知道，这很有趣
l don't know, it was all in good fun.
从哪里买？ 随便...
Where from? Anyway...
南希有一匹很漂亮的马
l think Nan's got a really nice mare. ...he's a wonderful new horse.
你的电话，先生 她说有急事
telephone call, sir. She said it was important.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
明天上午吗 你来不来
tomorrow morning? Do you wanna come?
该死的电话 整个周末就没有停过
that bloody phone has not stopped ringing all weekend.
没错 太烦人了
l know. lt's so irritating.
喂
Hello?
我打过你手机 但你关机了
l tried to call your mobile, but it's off.
你疯了? 打到这里来
Are you mad calling me here?
你什么时候过来
When are you coming over?
我尽量明天过去
l'm trying to make it for tomorrow.
我等不到明天了 我快要疯了
l can't wait till tomorrow, l'm going crazy.
到底是什么事 我怀孕了
What the hell's the matter? l'm pregnant.
我明天过去
l'll talk to you tomorrow.
我们要去试骑
'Oause we've got to go and try and look at this...
为克里斯选马 他们是从海军部门买来的
...horse for Ohris. they got it in the navy?
它缺乏蔬菜喂养
Yeah, the... lt was lack of enough vegetables, or something.
我想这也许是他们 采购柠檬和橘子的原因
l wonder if that's why they took lemons and oranges...
他们只有饼干
Well, they only had biscuits.
柠檬汁就是这样发明的
Well, that's where Rose's Lime Oordial originated...
谁打来的 萨曼塔, 我秘书
Who keeps calling? lt was Samantha, my secretary.
恐怕明天我不能骑马了 有些事要处理
l'm afraid l won't be able to go riding tomorrow. l can't help it.
萨曼塔不是说她这个周末 去看他父母的吗
l thought Samantha said she was going to her parents this weekend.
我知道，我把留下来工作了 可怜的孩子
l know, it's all my fault. Poor girl.
没什么大不了的
lt's no big deal.
我赶去城里
l'll pop back into town.
几个小时就可以搞定 不会再让它烦我了，我保证
the whole thing'll take a few hours, and it'll be off my mind. l promise.
真可惜 真不爽
that's a shame. lt's really sad.
太可怜了，因为
Well, it is a pity because l...
我也认为对萨曼塔是不公平的 坦白说
l think it's unfair on Samantha too, frankly.
是不应该
Yeah. Well, it's unfortunate,
但是 克里斯有太多事要处理了
but, you know, Chris has a lot of responsibility.
我们别说这个了
Well, anyway, let's not worry about it. Let's...
你这奴隶主 自从有人类文明以来
Slave driver. Look, as long as we make lamb bone.
你能... 行了，我认输
Oan you, can you...? Well, l think so.
怎么可能会怀上的 我跟你说了上个月的那个周末
How the hell did you get pregnant? l told you that weekend last month
我们要小心点 我没有做保护措施
that we needed to be careful and l didn't have protection,
但你不肯等
but you couldn't wait.
难以置信的背
What unbelievable bad luck.
天啊, 无论我怎么努力 都不能让我老婆怀孕
Ohrist, l can't get my wife pregnant no matter how hard l try,
而你没防范一会儿 我就中招了
and the minute you're unprotected l knock you up.
因为你爱我 不爱她
lt's 'cause you love me, and you don't love her.
那是你的理由吗
ls that your interpretation?
孩子是真正爱情的结晶
lt's a child conceived out of genuine passion,
而不是例行公事那样得来的
not as part of some fertility project.
好吧 我陪你去打掉它
Ok. Well l'll go with you, and we'll get it sorted.
我不能再那样做了 再?
l'm not doing that again. Again?
那是什么意思 这是第三次了
What's that supposed to mean? lt's the third time.
我年轻的时候做过一次 又为汤姆堕了一次
l did it once when l was younger, and then l did it for tom.
我不想打掉的 但他非要
l didn't want to, but he insisted.
诺拉 我想不出还有什么办法
Nola, l really can't see any other way.
为什么不能生下来 怎么养
Why can't l just have it? And what?
我们可以一起带大他 那是绝对不可能的
And we'll raise it together. that's obviously not possible.
为什么，你讨厌你的工作 你讨厌你的生活
Why? You hate yourjob, you hate your life.
我是说我们可以一起生活 孩子就是个祝福
l mean, it seems like a blessing. lt's a sign.
诺拉, 我得走了
Look, Nola, l have to go.
我编了六个谎言才能来这
l'm juggling six things at the same time
我得让事情看上去我没有骗人
just to make this trip to the city look legit.
我们星期二再谈
l'll talk to you on tuesday.
克里斯
Ohris...
你一定要... 我希望你可以快点解决这个
You must... l expect you to do the right thing, Ok?
我是不会罢休的
l'm not walking away from this.
是不是有什么事啊 整个周末都见你不开心
ls anything the matter? You seemed very gloomy all weekend.
我想和你谈谈 谈什么
l wanted to talk to you. What about?
我们
Us.
有什么问题吗
ls something wrong?
是的，有点
Yeah. there is.
是什么
What?
是市场规划失误的事吗
lf you're still taking a hammering financially in the market,
你知道那没关系的
you know it's not a problem.
我不能什么都依赖你父亲 克洛伊
l can't keep leaning on your father, Ohloe.
家庭和财富
Papa gets more pleasure out of helping his family,
爸爸更看重家庭 你知道的
than all the possessions he owns. You know that.
到底是什么
What is it?
是不是和你接的那些电话有关
ls it something to do with those phone calls you kept getting?
你每次讲完电话都有点怪怪的
Because you acted really strangely after each of them.
你在外面拈花惹草了?
Are you having an affair?
拈花惹草?
Am l having an affair?
是啊，拈花惹草
Yeah, that's what l asked.
没有 骗人
No. You are.
当然没有，别傻了
Of course l'm not. Don't be silly.
那你不再爱我了吗
Do you not love me anymore?
我当然爱你
Of course l love you.
那到底是什么事
Well, what's wrong?
我只是觉得让你失望了
l just feel like l'm letting you down.
没有啊，怎么会
You're not. How?
是不是因为我没有怀孕
ls it because l'm not getting pregnant?
我只是
l just...
觉得对不起你
...feel so guilty.
很对不起你
So terribly guilty.
听着, 克里斯
Listen, Ohris.
我们都去看过医生了 我们的身体没什么问题
We've both been to the doctor. We're both perfectly healthy.
我相信你完全有能力让我怀孕
l can conceive and you're perfectly capable of making a woman pregnant.
我从来都没有因为这事生过你的气
ls it me? Have l been horribly pushy and obnoxious on the subject?
我只是想要个孩子 想要个我们的孩子
Look, l... l just want a baby. l want to have our baby.
我们只是运气不好
We haven't been lucky yet, that's all.
克洛伊
Oh, Ohloe.
我们不要再讨论这个了
Let's get off the subject.
谈到生孩子 应该会让我们很高兴和兴奋才对
Having a child should be something that makes us both happy and excited,
而不是像现在这样那么紧张和焦虑
not a cause of all this tension and anxiety and...
我很想找个人吐吐苦水
l had to talk to somebody.
我很矛盾
l'm really suffering.
无论你和我说了什么 都不会有第三个人知道
Whatever you tell me goes no further.
我想为了一个女人离开我的妻子
l'm contemplating leaving my wife for another woman.
但每次话到嘴边
But when the time came to tell her...
却又说不出口
...l couldn't do it.
这个不是世界上最容易做的事 不是吗
Yeah, well, it's not the easiest thing in the world to do, is it?
这很疯狂
lt's crazy.
和那个女人没什么前途
l can see no real future with this other woman.
而且我和我老婆生活的很舒适
And l have a very comfortable life with my wife.
是啊，但如果你不爱她 我没有说我不爱她
Yeah, but if you don't love her... l'm not saying l don't love her.
只是感觉不一样
Just not in the way l feel about this other woman.
明白了
Right.
归纳起来就好象是性和爱的区别
Maybe it's finally the difference between love and lust.
但如果我离开克洛伊 我还能做些什么
But what the hell am l going to do if l leave Ohloe?
我还没有傻到不清楚 自己现在过的是什么生活
l don't fool myself that l haven't gotten used to a certain kind of living.
难道应该放弃这一切? 为了什么
Am l supposed to give it all up? For what?
为一个你爱的女人
ls it for a woman you love?
怎么生活，在哪里生活
to live how? Where?
做什么工作 这个嘛，看上去
to work as what? Well, it seems to me that you...
你已经很擅长做生意了
You're pretty good at what you're doing.
你可以重新找一个 和现在差不多的工作
there must be anotherjob in another firm that you can just, you know...
怎么可能 我现在是我老板的女婿
Let's face it, l'm the boss's son in law.
而且他那么疼我
And he loves me.
看上去这个女人并不足以
Doesn't seem to me like you want this other woman enough
让你放弃 你好不容易得来的这一切
to give up everything you've achieved for it.
我们要去度三礼拜假
We're going away for three weeks.
回来后我会和她坦白的 等你回来?
When l get back l'll tell her. When you get back?
那我怎么办 别敷衍我了
What am l supposed to do? Stop playing games with me!
我没有敷衍你 为什么你不现在就告诉她
l'm not playing games with you. Why don't you just tell her now then?
你不是说和她一起生活很虚伪吗
l'd think you'd want to stop living such a sham.
这很难开口 为什么
Look, it's not easy. Why not?
你已经厌烦了她 而且你每次都说
lf you're so bored at home with her and you're so crazy about me,
你爱的是我
which is all you ever tell me...
我不想把大家的假期都搞砸好不好?
l don't wanna mess this holiday up for everybody, Ok?
这是很大的打击
lt's a big blow.
对每一个人都会有巨大的影响
And it's gonna make a huge impact on everyone.
你怎么可以和一个
How can you go on vacation with a woman that you know you're gonna leave
假期一完你就和她离婚的女人去度假 小声一点
the minute you get back? keep your voice down.
你想知道我什么感受吗 我嫉妒，好吗
You wanna know how l feel? l'm jealous, Ok?
我不喜欢你和她做爱
l don't like the idea of you making love with her.
我不喜欢你和她旅行浪漫的样子
l don't like the idea of you going off island hopping with her. lt's romantic!
嘿，小声点
Hey, keep your voice down.
你知道我和她做爱
You know l make love to her.
只不过是例行公事
And you know it's just routine.
难道你就不能等几星期吗
For God's sakes, can't you wait a few weeks?
好吧
Yeah.
我只是要你和她说清楚
l just wanna know that something's gonna happen, you know?
我会的
lt will.
我会的 好
lt will. Ok.
假期取消了
the holiday's off.
为什么 怎么了
Why? What happened?
刘易斯要做手术
Maurice Lewis has to go in for an operation.
他怎么了
Why?
背上有一些碎片什么的 他没法走路
Disc in his back or something. He can't walk.
总而言之 要一段时间才能康复
Anyway, he needs recovery time
大家认为可以把假期推迟到夏季以后
and everyone thought we should just move it till after the summer.
我得把行李收拾一下
Let me just pack up my stuff.
我们可以步行去歌剧院 很近的
We should probably walk to the opera, it's so close.
好
Yeah.
喂
Hello?
机会来了, 克里斯
An opportunity has arisen, Ohris,
而且我认为对你有好处
which l think may be a lucrative one for you.
是吗
Really?
我们正在和一家日本公司协商
We're structuring something with a Japanese company.
这是一个独立项目 可以赚很多钱
lt's an independent operation. there's a great deal of money to be made.
我的看法是最先出资的人 将会获得暴利
And my thought was, anyone in on the ground floor stands to profit hugely,
如果预测正确的话
assuming our predictions are correct.
听起来不错 是的
Sounds exciting. lt is.
埃莉诺 我把这个好消息和克里斯说了
Eleanor. l've just told Ohris the good news.
但现在让我最开心的事 和钱不关
But what would make me the happiest has nothing to do with money.
我更喜欢让自己看上去 像一个年轻的奶奶
l'd like you to make me a young grandmother.
你已经是一个年轻的奶奶了
You already are a young grandmother.
没错 汤姆和希瑟有打算再给我生一个孙子
Yes. tom and Heather are trying for their second,
但我更想你成为妈妈
but l'd like you to be a mother.
好了 别那样看我
Oh, all right. Don't look at me like that.
不说就是了 你生日想要写什么
l'll be quiet. What would you like for your birthday?
我不知道 你生日?
l don't know. Your birthday?
很好嘛，你居然忘了
Great. You forgot.
其实没有 我已经买好礼物了
l didn't actually. l bought you something already.
看来我的暗示起作用了
So my hints worked.
妈咪 知道了，知道了
Mummy... l knew. l knew.
我们很努力了，我们不想... 好吧
We are trying. We don't want to... All right.
喂 克里斯
Hello? Ohris?
失陪一下 你随意
Excuse me. By all means.
我很生气 是的，亲爱的
l weigh as much as l did. Yes, darling.
别急好吗？ 我嘴巴太大了
Look, please relax, Ok? l spoke out of turn.
嘿，嘿 对不起，对不起
Hey. Hey. l'm sorry. l'm sorry.
你们俩在唠叨什么呢 没什么
What are you two bickering about? Nothing.
我告诉过你不要给我打电话 我会打给你的
l told you not to call me, l'd call you.
我一直在等你打来
Well, l... l... l was waiting for you to call.
我都等了一个礼拜了
l've been waiting a week.
这里到处都是人 我不方便说话
Well, there's always people around and l can't talk.
你什么时候回家
When are you coming home?
两礼拜后
ln about two weeks.
两礼拜? 你说整个旅行才三个礼拜
About two weeks? You said the whole trip was three weeks!
对啊，就三个礼拜啊
Yeah, right. three weeks.
克里斯, 爸爸和妈妈要走了
Ohris, Mummy and Papa are leaving.
马上，马上
Ok. Ok...
谁在说话 你到底在哪啊
Who is that? What country are you in?
你手机应该打不通的
Your mobile's been impossible.
跟你说了我在希腊
l told you. l'm in Greece.
周围都是人 我不方便说话
And there's always people around, so l can't talk.
我和快就回家了 回去再打给你
l said l'd be home soon, and l will call you.
我只是有点寂寞 我等不及了
l'm just lonely. l'm anxious.
你能不能
Oan you just...?
一回到家就和克洛伊摊牌
Please tell Ohloe as soon as you get home.
我只是想早点把这种情况解决
l just want this situation to be resolved.
你想我吗
Do you miss me?
好了 再见，再见
Ok. Bye, bye.
没什么事吧 没有，都很好
ls everything Ok? Yeah, everything's fine.
你们要走了吗 是的
Are you leaving already? Yeah.
克里斯，我是诺拉 你在哪里
Ohris, it's Nola. Where have l reached you?
撒丁岛
Sardinia.
五六天后就回来 好吗
l'll be back in five or six days, Ok?
早上好，约翰 你比以前早了啊，先生
Good morning, John. Oh, you're early, sir.
我这就去把车开来 好的
l'll bring the car around. Yes.
你骗我
You lied to me.
哦，天哪 你骗我
Oh, Jesus. You lied to me!
安静点 我要去找克洛伊
Quiet! l wanna see Ohloe!
Quiet, quiet. l wanna talk to Ohloe.
听着
Look, Ohrist, Ohrist.
不...听着 我可以解释
No, no, no, listen. Listen, l can explain.
我要去找克洛伊 你是个骗子，你是个骗子
l wanna talk to Ohloe. You're a liar! You're a liar!
我可以解释的 计程车
l can explain. l... taxi!
我不要跟你走 计程车
l'm not going anywhere with you. taxi!
我哪里也不去 冷静点
l'm not going anywhere with you. Oalm down.
诺拉，诺拉，冷静点 你是个骗子，你是个骗子
Nola! Nola, calm down. Oalm down. You're a liar! You're a liar!
我提前回来了 我提前回来了
l came home deliberately, l came home early.
你这个骗子 我要去找克洛伊
You're a liar! l wanna talk to Ohloe.
我要去找克洛伊 冷静点，冷静点
l wanna talk to Ohloe! Oalm down. Oalm the fuck down!
我要去找克洛伊 你这个骗子，你这个骗子
l wanna talk to Ohloe. You liar! You're a liar!
你是个骗子
You're a liar!
我提前回来了 因为这事让我受不了
l decided to cut the trip short because all this is eating away at me.
我前天才回来
l only came back the day before yesterday
我要一周没有你骚扰的时间
because l need a week in the city to deal with Ohloe
来慢慢和克洛伊说 你快要把我逼疯了
without you breathing down my neck. You're driving me crazy!
我不知道是否要相信你
l don't know whether to believe you or not.
相信我, 诺拉 你跟她说了吗
Please believe me, Nola. Well, did you tell her?
我刚要告诉她你就打来了
l was about to when you called.
跟打电话有什么关系
What does that have to do with anything?
我被你搅乱了 得了吧
l got flustered. Oh, please!
我正准备好要告诉她 你就打来了
l was all set to tell her and then you called,
我骗你还在希腊是我的错
and then l feel guilty about telling you that l'm still in Greece.
你说你在撒丁岛 我说的太快了
You said Sardinia. l... l was talking fast.
我不想让她知道我在讲什么
l... l didn't want her to know what l was talking about.
最终她还是要知道的
Well, she has to know eventually.
我开不了口 那让我来
l can't tell her. then l will.
诺拉，别这样
Nola, stop!
这太荒谬了 我们都有孩子了
Well, this is crazy. We're having a child together!
我们没必要非得要这个孩子
We don't have to have a child together.
没有这个孩子 我们会生活的简单点
lt would make life a hell of a lot simpler if we didn't.
对你简单 对我不是
Yeah, simpler for you, but not for me.
就算把孩子生下来
lt occurred to me that even if you had the child,
我也可以提供经济上的帮助 那样是不够的
l could help you out financially. that's not enough.
诺拉，讲点道理
Nola, be reasonable.
汤姆和我分手时也是这么说的
that's exactly what tom said when he broke off our engagement.
就是讲道理 才变成现在这个样子
Being reasonable got me where l am right now.
你是在威胁我吗
So, you're threatening me?
如果我没按你说的做 你可以去告诉我老婆?
lf l don't do what you say, you're gonna go to my wife.
你以前是骗我的吗
Were you lying to me?
所有那些你跟我做爱时
All those times we made love,
说的话 都是骗我的吗
all those conversations, were you lying to me then?
当然没有骗你 那就告诉克洛伊
Of course l wasn't lying. tell Ohloe.
一定得有人告诉她 你不做，就我来
Someone has to explain the situation. Either you do it, or l'll do it.
好，好 我会跟她说的
Ok, Ok. l'll do the right thing.
你们看见克里斯了吗
Have you seen Ohris?
一分钟前往那边去了
A minute ago. He went that way.
克里斯
Ohris?
你在哪，克里斯
Where are you, Ohris?
克里斯
Ohris?
克洛伊 是你吗
Ohloe, are you there?
你看见克里斯了吗
Have you seen Ohris anywhere?
没有 你可以上来一会吗
No. Oould you come up for a minute?
这套衣服我想你给点意见
l want you to give me some advice about this dress.
好的
Yeah, Ok.
我明天就告诉克洛伊
l'm telling Ohloe tomorrow.
你每天都这么说 每天都做不到
You say that every day, and you always back out.
然后我又得等多一天 我要结果，克里斯
l'm back where l started. l want something done, Ohris.
如果你没有勇气说 就让我来说
lf you don't have the nerve to do it, l'll do it.
你把这个作为对休伊特家族的复仇 是吗
that would be revenge for you against the whole Hewett family, wouldn't it?
你这样说什么意思
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
如果你想我跟克洛伊说 你就不用亲自跟她说了
My theory is you want me to tell Ohloe so you don't have to do it yourself.
天哪 你说的这么自然就好象
My God, it seems like you've had this whole thing checked out
做这个没什么负担是的 我也希望
by some psychiatrist. l wish.
我也希望有人来帮我们说 这所有事都是见不得人的
l wish had someone to confide in, but it's all so damn secretive.
克里斯 如果我不做点什么
Look, Ohris, if l don't do something about this,
我们一定会分开的 我都有你孩子了
we're gonna grow apart. l'm having your child!
我明天就跟她说, 诺拉 不然你还想我怎么样
l'm telling her tomorrow, Nola. What more do you want me to do?
现在就告诉她 今晚就告诉她
What more? tell her now! tell her tonight!
睡觉前跟她说我做不到 那不是好时机
l can't, not before she goes to sleep. lt wouldn't be the right time.
诺拉，我明天说
Nola, tomorrow is fine.
你明天什么时候回来 我都是6点半下班的啦
What time will you get back from work? Same time l always get off, 6:30.
那你6点三刻会在家吗
So you'll be home by a quarter to seven?
当然，克里斯 老是讨论这个，我恨死自己了
Yeah. Ohris, you make me say these things. l hate myself for them.
我只想我们在一起 我们会在一起的
l just want us to be together. We will be.
看芭蕾剧时 你太安静了
You were very nervy all through the ballet.
你不喜欢这部剧吗
Did you hate it?
不是，我只是有点不舒服 是吗
No, l'm just out of sorts. Yeah.
我还以为你昏过去了
l thought you were gonna pass out.
低血糖，一会就没事了
Low blood sugar. l'll be better soon.
今晚我还是不能和你做
l still can't do it with you tonight.
我那个还没完
l'm not over my little dose of whatever.
清洁工有没有把我的网球衫 放在你的工具包里
Did the cleaner put one of my tennis shirts in with your gear?
没有 你在做什么
No. What are you doing?
是吗，我看看
Really? Just let me have a quick look.
我哪里都找不到 别，让我来，让我来
l can't find it anywhere. No. Look, l'll check, l'll check.
我都整理好了的 我也不会弄乱的
l've got everything arranged in there. Ok. l wasn't gonna disturb anything.
我不知道还可能在哪里
'Oause l don't know where else it can be.
她老是把我的东西和你的搞混
She's always bloody mixing my stuff in with yours.
是这件吗
ls this it?
看，我就知道 她总是那么粗心
See, l knew it! She always bloody does that.
我得去和她说说
l've got to have words with her about it.
真是的
lt's really...
你把什么放进口袋了
What did you just put in your pocket?
哦，药盒而已 什么药盒
Oh, it's just my pill box. What do you mean a pill box?
药盒而已 你知道药盒是怎么样的
A pill box. You know what a pill box looks like.
让我看看 你在吃什么药?
Let me have a look at it. What pills are you taking?
不行，只是药盒而已 我需要它们
No, they're just my pills. l need them.
不...缓解压力的 因为你给我太多压力了
No, no, no, it's for stress, 'cause you stress me so much.
知道吗 什么
Guess what? What?
我买了明晚的戏票
l got tickets for the theater for tomorrow night.
不可能 一点都不像你
You haven't. that's not like you.
什么剧 《白宫女人》
What for? the Woman in White.
我听说很不错 我还以为你讨厌音乐剧
l heard it's great. l thought you hated musicals.
不，不是那样的
No, that's not so.
你喜欢这个音乐剧就行了 太棒了
And anyway, you love his music. Well, that's great.
我在剧院门口和你碰面吧
l'll have to meet you outside the theater,
我从画廊直接过去就行了
'cause l'll be coming straight from the gallery.
为什么不把司机带上
Why don't you take the chauffeur?
我叫计程车就行了 运气好的话我还可以玩一个小时网球
l'll grab a taxi, and with any luck l can get an hour of tennis in.
你真是太体贴了
You're so sweet.
你不知道我多想你对我这样好
You knew how much l wanted to see that.
好了，去睡觉吧 你也累了，亲爱的
All right, come to bed, because you're tired, my darling.
好的，马上
Ok, l will.
喂 喂，诺拉
Hello? Hello, Nola?
下班后就回家吧
When you get off work today, come right home.
我有一些好消息
l have some good news.
一切都处理好了 但电话上说不清楚
Everything's taken care of, but l'm reluctant to talk on the phone.
你下班后马上回来见我
You've got to meet me right after work.
我们得..计划计划
We have... plans to make.
好吧 我去把会见经纪人的事取消掉
Ok. l'll cancel my agent appointment.
很好，太好了
lt's good. this is good.
待会见，再见
l'll see you soon. Bye.
是他吗 是的
Was it him? Yeah.
你们得在前六个月准备好资金
So, you'll have to be prepared to cash flow the first six months.
是这样的吗，克里斯 是半年吗
ls that right, Ohris? A half year?
是的
Yes.
半年应该够了 说不定不用那么久
A half year should do it, maybe less.
好，非常好 下次见
Good. Jolly good. Well, see you next time.
好极了
Good.
我想你一定对他们项目的发展
Sayonara indeed. l thought you showed some interesting ideas there
提出了一些不错的意见
for developing their capacity.
我很高兴那起作用了 做的好，做的好
l'm excited about this venture, Rod. Good, good.
要去打网球吗 是的
Playing a little tennis later? Yes.
惊人的体能啊 享受其中吧
Amazing energy. Love it. Envy it.
什么事 你好，我是克里斯
Yes? Hello. l'm Ohris.
我是你邻居诺拉的朋友
l'm a friend of Nola's, your neighbor from next door.
我们上次见过
We met here last...
对不起 我不让陌生人进门的
l'm sorry, l don't let anybody in.
你不记得了吗 我们见过的
But... but, do you not remember? We met...
她问了你一些鼠害的事
She asked you something about your trouble with your mice,
你提到了花生酱
and you mentioned something about peanut butter.
哦，对，对
Oh, yes. Yes. Yes.
我叫克里斯·维尔顿 是网球教练
l'm Ohris Wilton, the tennis instructor.
有什么麻烦吗
Well, what's the trouble?
没有 我无意打扰你
No trouble at all really, and l... l don't mean to disturb you.
我只是想看看你家的电视接受情况
l was wondering if l could... could look at your tv reception.
诺拉那边的有点问题 电视吗
We seem to have trouble next door. Oh, with the tv?
是的
Yes.
我们有些小矛盾 今晚有诺拉最爱看的电视
We're getting some interference, and it's Nola's favorite tv night.
所以我不知道是屋顶的天线问题 还是我们电视的问题
So l don't know if it's the aerial on the roof or if it's us.
在那边 谢谢
lt's in there. thank... thank you.
我得去吃药了
l have to take my medicine.
以前没遇到过此类麻烦 一直都挺好的
there was no trouble before. l had it on and it was fine.
你上次不是说你叫哈里斯吗
Didn't you say your name was Harris?
艾斯比太太
Mrs. Eastby?
我是朗
lt's lan.
艾斯比太太
Mrs. Eastby?
艾斯比太太 我是朗
Mrs. Eastby? lt's lan.
我去街道商店 你要我帮你带点什么吗
l'm going down the corner shop. Oan l get you anything?
艾斯比太太 你还好吗
Mrs. Eastby, are you all right?
好啊，美女
Hi, princess. Hi.
你买到我推荐的那款CD机了吗
D'you ever get that portable OD player we talked about?
买到了 谢谢你的帮助
Yes, l did. thank you so much for helping me.
太好了
Excellent.
待会见，再见 再见
See you later. Bye bye. Ok. Bye.
诺拉
Nola.
对不起
Excuse me.
喂
Hello.
你在哪啊
Where are you?
马上就到了 两分钟
l'm almost there. l'll be two minutes.
晚上好
Good evening. Hello.
多少钱 2英镑
How much? that's two pounds, please.
2英镑
two pounds.
2英镑，这是我的票吗 是的，谢谢
two pounds. My tickets? Yes. thank you.
这里真是一团糟，长官
lt's a terrible mess in there, sir.
我想很容易就知道 这里发生了什么事
Well, l think it's pretty obvious what's happened here.
有人抢劫并杀害了这位老太太
Someone's robbed and killed the old lady.
当他或者他们跑出去的时候
As he, or they, were running out
刚好撞到赖斯小姐进来 出于惊慌
they've run into the Rice woman coming in, so they've shot her too.
他们把她也杀了
Either out of panic,
又或者他们抢了她后杀人灭口
or because they saw a chance to make an additional score.
可怜的家伙回家时间不对
Poor unsuspecting soul came home at the wrong moment.
房子里所有的处方药都没了
He's cleared out the house of all prescription drugs, sir.
毫无疑问这件劫案涉及毒品
Oh, no, it's definitely a drugs related robbery.
劫犯可能事先就知道8楼住着老太太
He might have known there was an old lady living in flat 8.
计划抢劫她
Probably cased her.
没想到另外一个女人撞了进来
Was surprised by running into the other woman.
她选择了错误的时间回家
She picked the wrong time to come home.
有些人就是没运气
Some people just don't have any luck.
对，我刚和她说过话 太难以置信了
Yeah, l just spoke to her. this is unbelievable.
半个小时前我下楼
Half an hour ago l came down the stairs,
顺便敲了艾斯比太太的门 因为
knocked on Mrs. Eastby's door 'cause l couldn't...
你需要汽车上的什么吗
Do you need anything from the car?
是的，叫验尸官快点来
Yeah. You can tell the exhibits officer to get a move on,
现场快被搞砸了 这个很重要
'cause this is getting ridiculous. Yeah, this is quite important.
她通常在今天烘烤 我想她可能用完了材料
She usually bakes today, and l thought maybe she'd run out of stuff.
所以我问她 需不需要帮她带点什么
So l asked her if she needed anything, and then
半个小时前? 你和她说过话? 她没应我
So, half an hour ago? Spoke to her? she didn't answer.
对，半个小时前 那时候罪犯一定还在里面
Yeah, half an hour ago. Yeah. So whoever it was, was still in there.
真可怕 真不敢相信
that's terrifying. l can't believe that.
你刚才和诺拉·赖斯说过话?
So someone was in there...? And you spoke to Nola Rice,
她说了些什么 打断一下
and did she say anything? Sorry to interrupt.
摄影师可以进去了吗
Oould we send the photographers in now, please?
不行，先等会
No, hang on. lf you just wait.
我们得先让验尸官进去取证
We've just got to get the exhibit officer in there first.
奎斯, 让摄影师在那等会
Ohris, Ohris, can you liaise with this man here?
等等 别让他进去
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Just catch him there.
我就在这里遇见诺拉
Well, l ran... Yeah, l bumped into Nola right here...
犯罪现场马上就要清理了 是吗
Scenes of Orime will be on their way very shortly, all right?
是的
Yeah... Yeah, l spoke...
我在这里遇到她 我们聊了两句
l bumped into her here. We talked and we chatted.
我以前向她推荐过一款音乐播放器
l recommended a piece of music equipment.
她买了 那是什么
She'd bought it. Yeah, and... Music equipment? What was that?
就是一款CD机 可以播放MP3，CD之类的
Nothing. lt was a portable OD player which reads MP3s, OD rewrites...
是毒品, 探长 他们为了毒品抢劫的
lt's drugs, guv. Someone after money for some drugs.
艾斯比太太不是很有钱啊
Well, Mrs. Eastby wasn't wealthy.
他们才不管 毒品
they don't care. Drugs?
对，绝对是毒品 他们为了钱抢劫
Yeah, definitely drugs. Someone after money for 'em, and...
如果他们想的话 他们会为了1英磅就杀了你
they'll kill you for a pound if they wanted to, you know.
这样的事真让人遗憾 不是吗
Well, it's a sorry state of affairs, isn't it?
是啊，老太太很少出门 基本上没什么冤家
Well, it's not as if the old lady had any enemies. She rarely went out.
猎枪干的 猎枪?
Used a shotgun. A shotgun?
猎枪很长 不是吗
that's a... that's a bit obvious, isn't it?
一定容易被看到 如果被锯短了呢
Somebody must've seen something. Oh, not if it was sawn off.
猎枪可以被弄的非常小 凯瑟琳，你不能停在那里
they can make them pretty small. Oatherine, love, you can't park there.
把那空出来 待会要放尸体
Leave that clear. We've got the SOOO coming down.
你喜欢昨晚的音乐剧吗
Did you like the musical last night?
是的，我喜欢 很有趣，优美的音乐
Yeah, l did. lt was good fun. Pretty music.
是啊，太棒了
Yeah, he's very good.
我要买票让爸爸和妈妈也去看
l'm gonna get tickets for Mummy and Papa.
好
Good.
哦，天哪 是什么，怎么了
Oh, my God. What? What is it?
哦，天哪 是诺拉
Oh, my God! Nola!
诺拉·赖斯 怎么了
Nola Rice. What?
她在一个入室抢劫案 涉及毒品的抢劫案中被杀了
She was killed in a burglary. A... a drugs burglary.
什么，嘿 让我看看
What? Here, let me see that.
天哪
Jesus Ohrist!
上面说，她下班回家
Apparently, she was coming home from work,
歹徒那时已经在那抢劫并杀了
and someone who was already there who'd burgled another flat and rob...
一个老太太 偶然撞见了诺拉
And shot an old lady, ran into Nola by chance, and...
她那时刚进入大楼 歹徒逃跑时向她开了枪
She was entering the building, and he was running out and he shot her.
天哪
Oh, my God.
喂
Hello?
知道了 我们刚刚看到
Yeah. Yeah, we've just this second read it.
太不可思议了吧
lsn't itjust terrible?
我从来对她都没好感 但这也太惨了
l never got along with her, but this is just tragic.
惨不忍睹 汤姆知道了吗
lt's tragic. Does tom know?
我刚打给他了 他也觉得不可思议
l've just called him. He can't believe it.
哦
l know.
等等，一定是他打来了 我待会打回给你
Wait, wait, that must be him. l'll call you back.
喂
Hello?
是的，我们刚看到 妈妈也打来了
Yeah, we've just read it, and Mummy just called.
是的，我知道 错误的时间，错误的地点
Well, yeah, yeah, l know. l mean, wrong place at the wrong time.
我想她一定是
l suppose she must've...
扰乱了歹徒或者歹徒们的计划什么的
l mean, disturbed a burglar or burglars, or whatever.
我是说，说不清楚 有几个歹徒
l mean, it doesn't... lt doesn't say how many of them there were.
就连妈妈也被吓坏了
Well, even Mummy's really shaken up,
就算她们不是朋友
and you know they weren't exactly friends.
这里说那个地区的毒品犯罪率 在过去一年里
lt says here that there's been a rise in drug related crime in the area
有所上升
over the past year.
你听到了吗，对
Did you hear that? Yeah.
我只是觉得不可思议 只是...我知道
l just can't believe it. lt's just... l know.
妈咪
Mummy.
我有事情告诉你
l've got something to tell you.
但得等到克里斯也在这
But l want Ohris to be here.
克里斯
Ohris?
他去哪了 我不知道
Where'd he go? l don't know.
刚刚还在这里的，克里斯
He was just in here. Ohris?
克里斯
Ohris?
他刚刚还在这里
He was just here.
说吧，你想告诉我什么
Well, what did you want to tell me?
等一下，克里斯
Just wait. Wait, wait. Ohris?
你在哪，克里斯
Where are you? Ohris?
你想告诉我什么
Well, what did you want to tell me?
我想等他到了再说
Well, l just really want him to be here.
来了
Hang on, there he is. there you are!
我们可以告诉她了吗 当然
Oan we tell her now? Sure.
我想你陪着我说嘛
Well, l wanted you to be here.
好了，什么事
Well, what is it?
妈咪
Mummy...
你终于可以为我开香摈了
You can finally crack open the champagne.
我怀孕了
lt looks like l'm pregnant.
你什么时候知道的 今天早上
When did you hear? this morning.
哦，我太高兴了 天哪
Oh, l'm so delighted. Oh, good.
阿莱克
Alec?
阿莱克，快到这来
Alec? Oome here.
我们都有点飘飘然了
We're both walking on air.
你当然飘飘然了 不过你老公有点震惊
Well, you're walking on air. Your husband looks a bit shell shocked.
是我把他累坏了，可怜的家伙 什么事
'Oause l've exhausted him, poor thing. What?
克洛伊怀孕了
Ohloe's pregnant.
今天是好日子啊 亲爱的，恭喜你
Oh, what a great day. Oh, my darling, congratulations.
我激动的打颤了 我真是太高兴了
l'm absolutely thrilled. l couldn't be more pleased.
多谢你雪中送炭
thank you so much. lt's such a relief.
不好意思，先生 不好意思
Excuse me, sir. Excuse me.
什么事 你的电话，你秘书
Yes? Phone call, sir. Your secretary.
真是太好了，不是吗 看看她，多开心啊
lt's wonderful, isn't it? Look at her, doesn't she look gorgeous?
玛格蕾，我怀孕了 恭喜你，太好了
Margaret, l'm pregnant! Oongratulations! that's wonderful.
谢谢你，玛格蕾
thank you, Margaret.
萨曼塔
Sam?
有个留言给你 迈克·班纳
Yeah, there's a message for you that a Mike Banner,
迈克·班纳探长找过你
Detective Mike Banner, called.
他叫你打个电话给他 他在石河布什警局
He wants you to call him at Shepherd's Bush police station.
我认为不急 但他留下了电话
Yeah. No, l don't think it's urgent, but he left a number.
班纳
Banner? Sweetheart...
我打赌是那个夜晚
l bet it was that night...
把号码给我吧
You better give me the number. Look, that's flattering.
上次你去，他说一切正常是吗
Well, the last time you went, he said everything was fine, didn't he?
是的，他让我完全放心了
Yes, and he just made me completely calm down.
难以置信，好极了
Oh, l just can't believe it. lt's marvelous.
谢谢你, 萨曼塔 再见
Ok. thanks, Samantha. Bye.
他有点古怪，有点不对劲
He just seemed odd, there was something weird.
奶奶要是知道会乐坏的 药物疗法
Granny would have been thrilled. ...alternative medicine.
奶奶肯定会高兴的 要是她在就好了
Granny would have loved it. l wish she could be here.
感谢上帝，感谢上帝 恭喜
thank God. thank God. Oongratulations!
请找迈克·班纳探长
Detective Banner, please.
这里是克里斯·维尔顿
this is Ohris Wilton.
你好
Oh, hello.
我是克里斯·维尔顿 你找我?
this is Ohris Wilton. You called?
哦，对 我想你能不能来我们这里一趟
Oh, yes. l was wondering if there was a time you could drop in here?
或者约个时间我们去找你也行
Or if it's more convenient, we can come and see you.
什么事 电话里一时也说不清楚
ln reference to what? l'd rather not explain on the phone.
只是问几个问题 我相信你会积极配合的
lt's just a few questions, and l'm sure you'd prefer it to be discreet.
没必要带律师，是吗
l've no reason to bring a lawyer, do l?
我希望不用
l certainly hope not.
克里斯·维尔顿，班纳探长 下午好
Ohris Wilton. Detective Banner. Good afternoon.
你好，请坐 谢谢
How do you do? take a seat. thank you.
没有什么好担心的
this is nothing to be alarmed about.
我们只是在对贝蒂·艾斯比 诺拉·赖斯谋杀案 做常规调查
We're just doing a routine investigation into the Betty Eastby Nola Rice murders.
你认识这两个受害者吗
Were you acquainted with either of the victims?
老实说 我认识诺拉·赖斯
Peripherally, l knew Nola Rice.
怎么认识的
How?
她以前和我大舅子订过亲
She was engaged for a time to the man who's now my brother in law.
那是...
that's...
汤姆·休伊特 是的
...tom Hewett? that's correct.
他们分手了 大约一年前
they broke up. A year ago. More.
你上次见到她是什么时候
When did you last see her?
天哪 我记不起来了
Oh, God, l can't remember.
在现代塔特 我和我老婆碰见过她
At the tate Modern. My wife and l ran into her.
很久以前的事了
But that was a long time ago.
那之后你有没有见过她
Have you seen her since?
好象没有
Not that l recall.
你有没有
Have...?
你有没有见过这个
Have you ever seen this?
没有，是什么
No. What is it?
你知道诺拉·赖斯一直在写日记吗
Are you aware that Nola Rice kept a diary?
不知道
No.
你看的到
As you can see...
写的全是你
...you're all over it.
是的，我看见了
Yes, l can see that.
你现在还坚称
Do you still claim that you haven't seen her,
一年前在现代塔特见过她后 就再没见过她了吗
except for more than a year ago at the tate Modern?
你不能怪我隐瞒 我和她交往的事
You can't blame me for trying to hide the fact that l had an affair with her.
而且你们也应该保护我的隐私
But you people have to protect me here.
我希望你不要 把我和她的谋杀案扯上关系
l hope you don't think l had anything to do with her murder.
你和她交往多久了
How long did your affair go on?
一次偶然的机会 在她还没和汤姆分开的时候
lt began casually when she was still engaged to tom.
他们分手后 她搬走了
they broke up, she moved away.
她回来后，我在现代塔特碰巧遇见她 然后我们又开始了
She came back and l ran into her at the tate Modern, and it began again.
请帮我保密
God, have a heart.
我妻子就要生小孩了
My wife is gonna have a baby.
她受不了这个的
this will devastate her.
你有
Did you...
答应过离开你的妻子而和 赖斯小姐结婚吗
...promise that you were going to leave your wife and marry Miss Rice?
不，没有
No, l did not.
也许她有那方面的幻想
l mean, it's possible she had that fantasy.
很明显，她上面写到了
And, obviously, she wrote that l did.
但我没有那样承诺过她
But l tried to finesse that point with her.
我不想和她结束性欲的关系
l didn't want the sexual relationship to end,
但我也不想破坏自己的家庭
but l'm not gonna break up my home.
我和我妻子好不容易才有个孩子
My wife and l are trying very hard to have a baby.
我们看了很多医生
We've seen several fertility doctors, et cetera.
你们可以去查查 但请你帮我保密
You can check that out if you like, but l beg you to be discreet.
但你误导了她
But you did lead her on,
她以为你在家里并不开心
so that she had the impression you were unhappy at home.
我试过不误导她
l tried to tip toe around it and not lead her on,
但她只相信她想相信的
but she's going to believe what she wants to believe.
请你们不要胡乱调查 以免破坏了别人的生活
Look, don't irresponsibly run roughshod over this and wreck people's lives.
我是说这案子和我没关系 因为我从不会伤害其他人
l mean, there is no case because l would not harm anyone,
诺拉·赖斯就更不会了
much less Nola Rice.
难道还不明显吗 有人杀了她的邻居
lsn't it obvious that somebody killed her neighbor,
她走进来时刚好看到
and she walked in when it was happening?
我请求你们 请别再调查我和她的事了
God, l beg you, don't go on a fishing expedition over this and...
因为你们正在破坏别人的生活
...wreck people's lives.
我的家庭, 我的婚姻危如累卵
My family, my marriage is at stake.
我们只是想查清楚这次谋杀案中 所发生的事
We just have to check out everything in a murder case.
那没问题 但我不是凶手
Ok, but l'm not your man.
我知道欺骗自己的妻子 是件不光彩的事
l know it's not the most honorable thing to cheat on your wife,
但并不说明我就是凶手
but that does not make me a murderer.
我们只是想查清楚案发过程
We're... obligated to review the situation.
我知道你对这事很敏感
l understand it's sensitive stuff for you.
但如果我们还要找你谈话的话
And if we have to talk to you again,
我们会尽量保密的
we'll do everything in our power to keep it very private.
你的私生活怎样是你自己的事
Your personal life's your own.
我们不做道德审判 只是调查案件而已
We're not making any moral judgments, just investigating a crime.
我能理解
l understand.
这样吧
Look...
如果你们还要找我谈话
...if you have to get in contact with me again,
虽然我希望不会了
which, God in heaven, l hope you don't,
请打我的手机
please call me on my mobile.
这是我的手机号
this is my number.
谢谢
thanks.
还有一件事
One other thing.
你拥有或有权利使用猎枪吗
Do you own or have access to a shotgun?
我?
Me?
没有
No.
我的岳父有, 我没有
My father in law shoots on the estate, but not me.
你们可以去查，但
You can check it out, but...
我请求你们顾及我和他的立场
...l beg you to consider mine and his position.
当然
Of course.
谢谢你
thank you.
你怎么看
So, what do you think?
我觉得就是他说的那样
l think it's what it looks like.
有人抢劫并杀了艾斯比夫人
Someone robbed and killed Mrs. Eastby,
惊惶逃跑时杀了诺拉·赖斯
who was surprised leaving, and killed Nola Rice.
我知道，我知道 上面写的是瘾君子做的案
Yeah, l know. l know, it's got drug robbery written all over it.
他就要做父亲了
He's 'specting a baby.
好吧，虽然她对妻子不怎么忠诚
Ok, he's not gonna win a medal for fidelity, but...
但我们可以去查查
...we can find out discreetly enough
休伊特家是否有有关联的猎枪
whether the Hewetts had a shotgun unaccounted for.
我不认为他会偷自家的枪
l don't think that he would know the first thing about stealing one though,
再把它锯短
never mind sawing one off.
这不太可能 他没有前科
lt's a bit of a stretch. He's got no previous convictions.
甚至没有拿过超速驾驶的告票
Not even a speeding ticket.
验尸官说艾斯比先被杀
the coroner says that Eastby was killed first.
是的 没有争斗的痕迹
Yeah. there's no sign of a forced entry.
所以艾斯比太太认识凶手 才让他进门的
So Mrs. Eastby knew the killer, if she let him in.
得了吧，迈克
Well, come on, Mike.
我们侦破的九成案件
Ninety percent of the crimes we go out on,
都是受害人自己让罪犯进门的
people open their doors and invite the criminals in.
我知道，你说的没错 我只是想不明白
Yeah, l know, you're right. l'm just thinking out loud.
他有真正的动机 也许
lt's just he's got a real motive. Yeah, maybe.
但你我都知道 有动机并不说明什么
But a motive, as you and l both painfully know, is not a case.
我只是对赖斯谋杀案有不同的看法
l'm torn because the Rice murder was clearly an afterthought,
我还想再深入调查一下
but l'd love to pursue it a little more.
但不想引起任何人的麻烦
But l'm reluctant to fish around and cause problems for everybody.
好吧，如果有新线索 我们再跟进吧
Well, if something develops, we can pursue it.
我怀疑到头来还是那个结果
l doubt anything's gonna drop into our laps.
克里斯
Ohris.
诺拉
Nola...
下这个决定并不好受
...it wasn't easy.
但当时机出现的时候 我扣了扳机
But when the time came, l could pull the trigger.
不到危急关头 你不会知道谁是你真正的朋友
You never know who your neighbors are till there's a crisis.
你要学着把罪恶感埋在心里 继续生活下去
You can learn to push the guilt under the rug and... go on.
必须这样
You have to.
否则它会吞噬你
Otherwise it overwhelms you.
那我呢
And what about me?
我这个做邻居的呢
What about the next door neighbor?
我和你们的恩怨毫无关系
l had no involvement in this awful affair.
为什么我这个清白人也要把命搭进去
ls there no problem about me having to die as an innocent bystander?
无辜者的牺牲有时候是 给大局铺路的
the innocent are sometimes slain to make way for a grander scheme.
你就是个无辜的牺牲者
You were collateral damage.
诺拉肚里的孩子也是
So was your own child.
索福克勒斯（希腊悲剧诗人） 说过
Sophocles said:
"不出生在这个世上...
'to never have been born
也许是最完美的结果"
may be the greatest boon of all.'
准备受到报应吧 克里斯
Prepare to pay the price, Ohris.
你做的太差劲了
Your actions were clumsy.
到处都是漏洞
Full of holes.
人们很容易就可以找到证据
Almost like someone begging to be found out.
如果我被抓到被判罪了
lt would be fitting if l were apprehended
也是应该的
and punished.
说明这世上还有点正义
At least there would be some small sign ofjustice.
还有点
Some small...
希望存在的可能
...measure of hope for the possibility of meaning.
克里斯·维尔顿杀了她们 我梦见他怎么做的了
Ohris Wilton killed them. l see how he did it.
什么
What?
就和我们推测的那样
lt's as we speculated
一切都很精细 但凶手一定是他
and said was too elaborate, but that's what he did.
她先杀死隔壁的邻居 然后为了毁掉证据
He killed the next door neighbor first to throw us off the scent
制造了抢劫的假象
and set up the appearance of a robbery.
他在那里等着
He waited in the hall.
他知道她会什么时候回来
He knew she'd be back the same time as usual,
然后他杀了她 弄的像是她遇到了抢劫杀人贩
and he killed her, making it seem like she surprised a burglar running out.
他设计好了一切 他准时出现在剧院
He planned it all so he could make the theater in time
以制造他不在场证据
to strengthen his alibi, if one became necessary.
虽然我还没想通猎枪的问题
Now, l haven't figured out the weapon problem,
而且还要和陪审团费很多口舌
and l know it's a lot to ask a jury,
但这都是我做梦时 看到的案件真相
but the correctness of it came to me in my sleep
我要推翻这个案子
and l am going to break this case.
我讨厌成为传递坏消息的人 迈克
l hate to be the bearer of bad news, Mike.
什么
What?
你的梦可不是陪审团现在最感兴趣的
Not that your dream isn't of primary interest to a jury.
什么坏消息
What's the bad news?
凌晨4点那个地区又发生了件枪杀案
there was another shooting in the area last night, 4am.
一个瘾君子被杀了 看上去是毒品交易不怎么顺利
A drug addict killed. Looks like a drug sale turned nasty.
那又怎样，难道他死前承认 是他杀了那两个女人吗
What, and he confessed to killing two women before he died?
没有 没必要说
No, he didn't have to.
但在他的口袋里 找到了老太太的结婚戒指
the old woman's wedding ring was right in his pocket.
不可能 戒指上刻有名字和日期
No. Name and date engraved right on it.
我不信 我理解，我理解
l don't believe it. l know. l know.
你调查的很不错 克里斯有很多动机
Your case looked good, lots of motive.
但他的动机也很明显 就是海洛因
But his motive was pretty strong too. Heroin.
那个瘾君子有一大堆前科
Junkie with a long string of convictions.
毫无疑问 他被黑吃黑了
killed by one of his own, no doubt.
走吧 我请你吃早餐
Oome on, l'll buy you breakfast.
你可以继续说说你的梦
You can traumatize me with the rest of your dreams.
不，等等
No, wait.
如果是维尔顿干的 事后他把珠宝扔了，而那个人捡到了呢
What if Wilton did it, threw the jewels away, this guy finds them?
我不知道 看看今晚你能梦见些什么吧
l don't know. See what tonight's dream tells you.
我想陪审团一定会感兴趣的
l'm sure a jury will be interested.
走吧
Oome on.
我放弃了
l give up.
我知道不是维尔顿干的
l knew Wilton didn't do it.
他只是个欺骗老婆的可怜虫
He's another poor schmuck who cheated on his wife.
当你看了诺拉·赖斯的照片后 你就知道为什么了
When you see those pictures of Nola Rice, you can see why though.
什么世界啊，是吧
What a world. Am l right?
小心，小心 我老是怕这些会掉下来
Oareful, careful. l'm always afraid they'll drop.
别杞人忧天了，爸爸 婴儿太..柔软了
Oh, chill out, Dad. Babies are so, so soft.
对了，香槟
Right. Ohampagne.
他的眼睛像你，克洛伊 是吗
l think he's got your eyes, Ohloe. Really?
我觉得他和你好像 真的
l think he's got your coloring darling, l really do.
妈咪，现在说不准的 他长的时候会变的
Mummy, you can't tell anything yet. they change all the time.
我的外甥 汤姆，汤姆舅舅
My nephew. Uncle, Uncle tom.
哦，这些花好漂亮 天啊，他看起来很像克里斯多佛
Oh, look at these flowers. No, he does look like Ohristopher.
事实上，说起那个 你有没有得到艾伦·辛克莱的职位
Actually, speaking of which, didn't you move into Alan Sinclair's old office?
狗屎运 妈妈，他在做梦耶
You lucky swine. Oh, Mummy, look, he's dreaming.
我们也要生第二个了
Let's work on number two. Oome on.
快看，他帅呆了 看他的脸
Oome on, he is a handsome boy. Look at that face.
是啊，他很英俊
Yeah, he's gorgeous.
这边，来了 埃莉诺，让一让
Right, here we are. Eleanor. Please...
克洛伊 好极了，爸爸
Ohloe... Good stuff, Papa.
喝酒了
thank you, darling. there you are. there we go.
没问题，你待着别动 我来递给大家吧
lt's all right, you stay there. l'll pass them round, shall l?
请
Please do.
宝贝，拿着
What a good idea. Darling, have one.
敬特伦斯·维尔顿 对
to terence Elliot Wilton. Yes.
有克洛伊和克里斯这样的父母
With parents like Ohloe and Ohris,
这个孩子无论想做什么 都会有所建树的
this child will be great at anything he sets his mind to.
谢谢，妈咪 肯定是的
thank you, Mummy. He will. He...
我不在乎他是否杰出
Do you know what, l don't care if he's great.
我只希望他运气好
l just hope that he's lucky.
不错 说的好
Oh, lovely. What a lovely thought.
他运气肯定好 太可爱了
He probably will be. Absolutely adorable.
妈咪，我现在就可以喝酒了吗 可以，可以
Mummy, are you sure l'm allowed this? Yes, yes.
可以，当然可以
Yes, of course you are. You haven't had any for months.
可以的话，我把他让你抱了
l'd get it down you now, while you can.
他帅吗？他真帅
lsn't he handsome? My God, he's handsome.
我敢和你打赌 下一个一定是女孩
Bet you any money the next one's a girl.
你们说他什么
What are you saying about him?
说他长得很漂亮
l was just saying he's got the most adorable cheeks.
我们在说他有多帅 帅得不平凡
We were just saying how handsome he is. Just so extraordinarily handsome.
我想知道他在想什么
l wonder what he's thinking.
护士们都说他爱思考
Well, you know, they said he was a thinker. the nurses.
沉思者 我们在此
Deep thoughts. Deep thoughts. Here we are.
敬特伦斯 敬特伦斯
to terence. to terence.
敬特伦斯 祝他一生好运
to terence. And all that sail on him.